<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[18]]></id><name><![CDATA[atos3x]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIPS 3x Atos Worldline]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Creditcardbetaling of Walletbetaling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Accept payments divided into 3 installments with no fees, with the SIPS - 3 installments no fee module. PayLib and 3D Secure included]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/creditcardbetaling-walletbetaling/18-atos-sips-3x.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Accept payments divided into 3 installments with no fees, with the SIPS - 3 installments no fee module. PayLib and 3D Secure included.  This module is available for&nbsp;merchants located in France ONLY.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rateAdapt to all your customersAttract new customers]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[7.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[299.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[379.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[269.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595263-pprod/atos-sips-3x.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595263-pbig/atos-sips-3x.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[685]]></id><name><![CDATA[productmedia]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Productgebonden media (Audio / Video)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Video's & Muziek]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[﻿Verrijk uw productsbeschrijvingen&nbsp;met toelichtende video&rsquo;s en video- of audio-previews!  Met de module Product Media kunt u uw&nbsp;eigen media importeren&nbsp;(audio- en videobestanden) e]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/video-s-muziek/685-productgebonden-media-audio-video.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/685.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[﻿Verrijk uw productsbeschrijvingen&nbsp;met toelichtende video&rsquo;s en video- of audio-previews!  Met de module Product Media kunt u uw&nbsp;eigen media importeren&nbsp;(audio- en videobestanden) en&nbsp;eenvoudig&nbsp;aan uw productpagina&rsquo;s toevoegen.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Maak uw productpagina&rsquo;s interactiever en uw producten toegankelijkerGeef meer informatie over uw producten: voordelen, een betere beschrijving, aanbevelingen voor gebruik, enz.Verbeter gemakkelijk uw conversiepercentageVerhoog uw omzet en verminder het aantal producten dat wordt teruggestuurd]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611425-pprod/productgebonden-media-audio-video.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611425-pbig/productgebonden-media-audio-video.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Kruisverkoop & Pakketaanbiedingen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Maakt de verkoop van partijen mogelijk met behulp van voorraden van daadwerkelijke beschikbare producten waaruit uw pakketten samengesteld zijn en biedt de mogelijkheid bedrijfsactiviteiten toe te pas]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/kruisverkoop-pakketaanbiedingen/1015-advanced-pack-5.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Maakt de verkoop van partijen mogelijk met behulp van voorraden van daadwerkelijke beschikbare producten waaruit uw pakketten samengesteld zijn en biedt de mogelijkheid bedrijfsactiviteiten toe te passen.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Maak de aankoop van combinaties van producten met of zonder een korting mogelijk met één klik  Wilt u de inhoud van uw gemiddelde winkelwagentje vergroten en tegelijkertijd uw klanten geld doen besparen als ze verschillende producten op hetzelfde moment kopen? Dat is nu mogelijk dankzij het Geavanceerd Pakket!  Zonder langer te hoeven wachten, kunt u productpakketten creëren die met één klik gekocht kunnen worden zonder dat u zich zorgen hoeft te maken over hun voorraad of combinaties.   Een waardevol aanvullend verkoopinstrument  Begeleid uw klanten in hun aankoopproces door hen pakketten van coherente producten aan te bieden die u vooraf bepaald heeft net zoals een verkoper dat zou doen in een echte winkel. Zoals bijvoorbeeld: deze fantastische camera, geheugenkaart en driepoot. U weet dat dit een geschikte selectie is en dat het uw klanten zal aanspreken.  Of u kunt zelfs uw bestsellers gebruiken door ze te koppelen aan producten die minder zichtbaar zijn zodat uw klanten die ook kunnen ontdekken.  Uw pakketten moeten tenminste uit twee producten bestaan maar het aantal is onbeperkt.  Verhoog de hoeveelheid per product en kies de combinaties die u wilt. Er zijn verschillende opties waarmee u de mogelijkheden kunt vermenigvuldigen.    Wilt u de aankoop van een product binnen een pakket reserveren? Dat is ook mogelijk! Hiervoor kunt u een gratis product aanbieden indien het gekocht wordt als onderdeel van een pakket. De mogelijkheden zijn oneindig!  Geïntegreerde assistent  Het ligt niet altijd voor de hand te beslissen welke producten er in een pakket moeten worden aangeboden. Maar hiervoor biedt het Geavanceerde Pakket opnieuw de oplossing voor het probleem. Wanneer u uw pakket creëert, zal onze module u van strategische informatie voorzien zoals het aantal verkochte producten of hun beschikbare voorraad.  Er is ook een geïntegreerde dynamische prijssimulator voor uw pakket die u meer duidelijkheid biedt bij het creëren van uw zakentransactie zonder dat u uw winstmarge in gevaar brengt.  Blijf meester van uw combinaties  Een van de producten die u aan uw pakket toegevoegd heeft, is beschikbaar in verschillende kleuren maar u wilt ze niet allemaal aanbieden in deze set? Met het Geavanceerde Pakket kunt u dit doen.  U zult ook de mogelijkheid hebben om een standaardcombinatie op voorhand te bepalen voor elk van de producten van uw pakket zelfs als ze verschilt van de combinatie bepaald in uw catalogus.   Uw klanten kunnen dan hun selectie personaliseren met de kenmerken die u gekozen heeft om te integreren in de aanbieding.  Zakenstimulans   Stimulans is iets dat uw bezoeker motiveert om een aankoop te doen. Het hoofddoel is om meer bezoekers op uw website ertoe aan te zetten hun bestelling te finaliseren en/of meer geld per transactie te spenderen. Misschien heeft u dit al geprobeerd door gratis levering aan te bieden bij aankopen van meer dan een bepaald aantal producten of door kortingen op bepaalde producten te geven of misschien zelfs door kortingsbonnen te verzenden?  Al deze methodes werken, maar hun bereik is beperkt aangezien dergelijke promoties normaal gezien tijdelijk zijn door hun buitensporige kosten! Stop met zoeken, u hebt de oplossing al gevonden!  Om uw klanten te verleiden zal het Geavanceerde Pakket u de keuze geven een korting aan te bieden wanneer alle producten in het winkelwagentje besteld zijn waardoor dus de aankoop van het volledige pakket gestimuleerd wordt.  Er zijn 3 mogelijkheden beschikbaar: een bepaalde korting op elk product in het pakket aanbiedeneen algemene korting op de set producten aanbiedeneen vaste prijs toepassen zoals bijvoorbeeld een psychologische prijs Met het Geavanceerde Pakket kunt u ook de kortingen die u al op uw producten gegeven heeft kunnen beheren door ze te integreren in de prijs van het pakket, of ze daarentegen uit te sluiten zodat de vooraf vastgestelde korting op het pakket gekozen wordt. Deze beslissing zal zelfs makkelijker gemaakt worden door onze duidelijke en ordelijke interface waarmee u de producten met kortingen heel gemakkelijk kunt bekijken.  U hoeft zich geen zorgen meer hoeven te maken over de coherentie van uw prijzen  Heeft u ooit al eens alle prijzen in uw catalogus moeten herzien om mogelijke incoherenties te vinden en ze te verbeteren? Wat zou er gebeuren indien u handmatig de gevolgen van deze wijzigingen in de productprijzen in uw pakketten zou moeten aanpakken? Dit zou een aanzienlijke extra werklast met zich meebrengen indien het niet geanticipeerd werd binnen de keuze van managementoplossingen in uw pakketten!  En opnieuw heeft het Geavanceerde Pakket de oplossing.  Indien er geen korting van toepassing is, is de prijs van het pakket standaard de som van de producten waaruit het pakket bestaat.  Indien u de prijs van een product moet wijzigen nadat het pakket gecreëerd is, zal de prijs van het pakket automatisch gewijzigd worden zonder dat u daar iets hoeft aan te doen.  In die gevallen waarin u een korting toekent aan een of meerdere producten in een bestaand pakket en op voorwaarde dat u de promotionele implicaties heeft geautoriseerd, zal de prijs van het pakket ook veranderen en de korting die toegepast wordt, zal aan uw klanten getoond worden.  Is een van de producten in uw pakket onderhevig aan een groene belasting? Geen probleem, dit zal automatisch weergegeven worden in de prijs van het pakket en het zal duidelijk vermeld worden waardoor volledig respect voor de wetgeving gegarandeerd is.  Wat het beheer van uw voorraad betreft, alles verloopt automatisch!  Voor elk pakket dat besteld wordt, zullen de producten van de voorraden automatisch afgetrokken worden. Op die manier zult u dubbel voorraadbeheer of de frustratie die voortvloeit uit onmogelijke verkopen door een slechte toewijzing van hoeveelheden kunnen vermijden.  Ook in het geval dat er een product uit een pakket niet meer voorradig is, zal het automatisch weergegeven worden als onbeschikbaar voor verkoop dankzij een waarschuwingssysteem voor de beschikbaarheid dat zowel elegant als modern is.  We hebben een grafisch en leuk meldingssysteem geïntegreerd voor uw klanten waardoor voorraadtekorten van combinaties of producten in het pakket onmiddellijk zichtbaar zijn. Er bestaat geen enkele kans dat u bestellingen ontvangt voor producten die niet voorradig zijn!  Accentueer uw pakketten en verkoop meer  Zodra u uw pakket bepaald heeftt, kunt u het op dezelfde manier configureren zoals u dat zou doen met een klassiek product. Alles is mogelijk, zoals het pakket voorzien van aangepaste afbeeldingen, het pakket classificeren in uw gewenste categorie, uw zoekmachineoptimalisatie verbeteren, een aangepaste beschrijving schrijven, een EAN-code of een specifieke referentie eraan toekennen, het volume ervan configureren om de leveringskosten te berekenen, enz...  Voor wie niet echt veel tijd heeft en zijn marketing wil vergemakkelijken, zal het Geavanceerde Pakket automatisch alle foto's van de producten in het pakket weergeven net zoals de beschrijvingen in de vorm van tabs. Uw klanten zullen correct geïnformeerd worden zonder dat ze de pagina van uw pakket hoeven te verlaten en kunnen hun aankoop voltooien met één klik.  En dat is nog niet alles... Voor een betere zichtbaarheid zullen uw pakketten automatisch geaccentueerd worden op hun gegevensbladen voor diegene die in partijen verkocht worden. Op die manier zult u uw klanten ertoe aansporen eerder een pakket te bestellen dan enkel het product waarin ze eerst geïnteresseerd waren. Dit is in feite kruisverkoop: een toegankelijke methode om de inhoud van uw gemiddelde winkelwagen te vergroten!  We zijn de ontwerpers niet vergeten  Vanaf het begin hebben we er rekening mee gehouden dat deze module gemakkelijk geïntegreerd moet kunnen worden door uw webagentschap of -ontwerper/-integrator. De module past zichzelf perfect aan aan de standaardthema's van PrestaShop 1.5 en 1.6 terwijl de meest geavanceerde grafische personalisatie mogelijk is.    Er wordt een set JavaScript-sjablonen en CSS-opmaaksjablonen geleverd als modellen samen met de module om het integratieproces te vergemakkelijken. Uzelf of uw integrator zal dus in staat zijn alle functies van het Geavanceerde Pakket 5 te gebruiken, om ze in de grafische vorm weer te geven die het best overeenkomt met de algemene sfeer van uw onlinewinkel.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[319.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[224.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1048]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsshoptab]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Shop for Fan Page]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Produkten op Facebook & sociale netwerken]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Set up a "Shop" tab on your Facebook page and increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website. Boost your Facebook community]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/produkten-facebook-sociale-netwerken/1048-advanced-shop-for-fan-page.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1048.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Set up a "Shop" tab on your Facebook page and increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website. Boost your Facebook community.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[*** WINNER OF THE 2011 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  Show your products directly on the social network. Effective way to boost your sales, enjoy the power of your Facebook community to communicate about your shop and increase the number of visitors and orders on your PrestaShop store. Important note : the shop tab set up by our module is independant of the default shop tab already installed by Facebook in your page. The module creates a new tab that you can name as you want !  LEVERAGE THE POWER OF YOUR FACEBOOK CUMMUNITY TO GENERATE TRAFFIC AND SALES ON YOUR SHOP Increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website and boost your Facebook community. It’s a real way to grow your sales: take advantage of your Facebook community to communicate and bring your audience to your shop. This module is compatible with the multishop feature."Advanced Shop for Fan Page"&nbsp;is also compatible with most shared SSL certificates (certified to work with OVH shared SSL hosting) The module also lets integrate statistics tracking via Google Analytics to measure its performance A live built-in preview of the module will help you set it up, and you can then easily link it to your Facebook page in a single click. "Advanced Shop for Fan Page" will help you improve your brand image and reach.  INCREASE THE NUMBER OF « LIKES » ON YOUR PRODUCTS AND THEIR VISIBILITY For each product, a "Like" button is included, which will allow visitors to share and talk about your products. Clicks on"Like" buttons will have impact on your website’s SEO and its position in Google search results. We also offer you to go even further : use your Google Analytics code to get your statistics as to the effectiveness of your Facebook Shop.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963149-pprod/advanced-shop-for-fan-page.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963149-pbig/advanced-shop-for-fan-page.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Bezorging volgen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Gebruikt u de bezorgdienst van UPS, een transporteur die bekendstaat om zijn snelheid en betrouwbaarheid?  Maak het uzelf gemakkelijk en verhoog de klanttevredenheid met de UPS-module met tracering, w]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/bezorging-volgen/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Gebruikt u de bezorgdienst van UPS, een transporteur die bekendstaat om zijn snelheid en betrouwbaarheid?  Maak het uzelf gemakkelijk en verhoog de klanttevredenheid met de UPS-module met tracering, waarmee u uw zendingen in de hele wereld kunt volgen.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Profiteer van de diensten van UPS en de traceermodule:Lever al uw pakketten in binnen- en buitenland dankzij de betrouwbaarheid van het distributienetwerk van UPS.Profiteer van een geavanceerde tracering van uw zendingen, stap voor stap, gewoon vanuit uw backoffice.Verkort uw bezorgtijden en verbeter de algemene koopervaring van uw klanten door te zorgen voor een optimale bezorgkwaliteit.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1768]]></id><name><![CDATA[gmerchantcenter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prijsvergelijkers]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/prijsvergelijkers/1768-google-merchant-center-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1768.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.&nbsp;The performance of Google AdWords Shopping campaigns and your presence in the &quot;Shopping&quot; results of Google&#39;s search engine largely depends on the quality of your Google Merchant Center feed and completeness of your data. The more information accurate you include, the better the results ! This very complete module will let you achieve just that and maximize your chances of obtaining good rankings on Google Shopping, while minimizing the time you will need to spend to have all your products accepted by Google.&nbsp;Instantly boost your traffic : Google Shopping and AdWords benefit from hundreds of millions of hits each month. Moreover this traffic is highly targeted and brings qualified visitors to your shop&nbsp;Increase your sales and ROI : Because traffic is extremely targeted, Google Shopping and Google AdWords Shopping Campaigns provide you with one of the highest return on investment rates compared to other marketing channels and is very cost effective&nbsp;About your products export, the power of the module allows you to only focus on the configuration of a single product feed (a primary feed) and not to waste time with the configuration of &quot;supplemental feeds&quot; and numerous &quot;rules&quot; provided by Google. You modify your product information directly in the module and you have the possibility to automate the update of all your data in Google Shopping, daily.&nbsp;Present in over 37 countries as of today, Google Shopping is a fast track start for international expansion&nbsp;&nbsp;With more than 6000 copies sold, 510+ reviews and an average 4.7/5 rating, our Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping) module is hands down the most robust, accurate, powerful and complete module for Google Shopping.&nbsp;We also have extensive knowledge and experience on the ins and outs of Google&#39;s rather complex requirements, and our tech support team will gladly help answer your questions to the best of their ability !&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For power users and SEM agencies, for even more great features, including advanced custom labels management, promotions feed and quick inventory feed, you may be interested in purchasing the PRO version of the module available on&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/price-comparison/20908-google-merchant-center-pro-google-shopping.html&nbsp;&nbsp;This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the&nbsp;2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for &quot;Best module&quot;, with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module.&nbsp;Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support&nbsp;: when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.7.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[149.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/963144-pprod/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963144-pbig/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2072]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedtopmenu]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu - Responsive]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Menu]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Discover and choose the most popular and more powerful responsive mega menu for PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/menu/2072-advanced-top-menu-responsive.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2072.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Discover and choose the most popular and more powerful responsive mega menu for PrestaShop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu&nbsp;allows you to build all types of horizontal navigation bars: single bar, drop-down menus, rich menu, mega-menu with columns.&nbsp;Advanced Top Menu&nbsp;is a PrestaShop Addon that will help you to simplify the navigation and usability of your website. Give to your visitors an&nbsp;overwiew of your catalog&nbsp;making them to quickly find the desired product.&nbsp;Thanks to its&nbsp;highly modular design, you will be able to use your menu bar to display images, promotions or advertisements, and&nbsp;put forward your offers and services&nbsp;that make your store unique.&nbsp;With a rich configuration interface, it makes you able to customize your menu bar&nbsp;without special technical knowledge:ResponsiveUnlimited number of tabsUnlimited number of columnsUnlimited number of elementsSimple and complete graphical customizationAutomatic menu generation from your catalogAll content types supported: categories, manufacturers, suppliers, CMS, custom links...Conditional display depending on the status of your visitor&nbsp;A faster and cleaner configuration&nbsp;interfaceNew default&nbsp;theme for optimal&nbsp;design out of the boxNew appearance settingsNew specific settings for mobileA&nbsp;Sticky mode, which let your menu always visible regardless of scroller&nbsp;positionAllows you to restrict the display of some elements for desktop or mobile viewAllows you to add different images for each languageOpening animation effect on submenusDelay on opening submenusContextual help tips in Back Office]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.12.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573526-pprod/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573526-pbig/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2376]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestagiftvouchers]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Kortingsbonnen]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Loyaliteitsprogramma]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Bind uw geregistreerde klanten door &nbsp;waardebonnen &nbsp;aan te bieden die zij bij hun volgende aankoop kunnen besteden!  Met deze complete, eenvoudig te installeren module, genereert u kortingsbo]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/loyaliteitsprogramma/2376-kortingsbonnen.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2376.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Bind uw geregistreerde klanten door &nbsp;waardebonnen &nbsp;aan te bieden die zij bij hun volgende aankoop kunnen besteden!  Met deze complete, eenvoudig te installeren module, genereert u kortingsbonnen die u automatisch kunt sturen naar klanten die via hun account een bepaald soort bestelling hebben gedaan: minimumbedrag, aankoop van een specifiek product of een product binnen een speciale categorie, u beslist wat voor u het handigst is!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Loyalty&nbsp;Discount Vouchers module you can:  &nbsp;Automatically create cart rules that generate offer codes emailed to your customers,&nbsp;Customize the coupons&rsquo; name, their value as a percentage or amount as well as their validity period,&nbsp;Increase average cart size on your site by defining minimum purchase amounts in order to use the discount voucher,&nbsp;Build customer loyalty by encouraging customers to buy again from your store,&nbsp;Easily liquidate your inventory of products of your choice, and better promote your new products and categories]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708607-pprod/kortingsbonnen.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/708607-pbig/kortingsbonnen.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marktplaats (marketplaces)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/marktplaats/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world’s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.  Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.  The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons  since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.2.253]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[249.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Zoeken & Filteren]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[De beste module voor facetnavigatie voor PrestaShop ! Winnaar van de Best Modules Awards]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/zoeken-filteren/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[De beste module voor facetnavigatie voor PrestaShop ! Winnaar van de Best Modules Awards]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Een onmisbaar hulpmiddel voor winkels die een groot assortiment aan producten aanbieden, Advanced Search 4 laat toe om zoveel zoekengines toe te voegen als u zelf wenst en om ze te plaatsen op locaties naar keuze. &nbsp; De zoektechniek van deze module is gebaseerd op filters. Ze zijn gebaseerd op &rsquo; een beproefde facetnavigatie. Ze laten uw klanten toe om producten terug te vinden die voldoen aan hun criteria in zo weinig mogelijk klikken. Advanced Search 4 werd ontwikkeld met het oog op kortere laadtijden, zelfs voor catalogussen met meerdere tienduizenden producten of categorie&euml;n. &nbsp; Eerste versie uitgebracht in 2010 - Winnaar van de Best Modules Awards in 2012 - Sinds 2010 beschouwd als een van de beste sales add-ons. &nbsp; Er staan 3 soorten opzoekingen ter uwer beschikking:Zoeken in de volledige catalogus: de zoekperimeter maakt gebruik van de volledige catalogus.Zoeken in een selectie van producten: de zoekperimeter beperkt zich tot de pagina waarop de klant zich bevindt.Zoeken in stappen: de criteria verfijnen zich en tonen resultaten aan de hand van wat u klanten aanduiden in hun zoekopdracht.&nbsp; Bovenop haar hoofdfunctie, is de module Advanced Search eveneens gekend als een van uw beste bondgenoten voor verwijzingen. Er is een ge&iuml;ntegreerdegenerator voor pagina&#39;s geoptimaliseerd voor SEO, die u toelaat om uw zichtbaarheid te vergroten en dit allemaal zonder dubbele inhoud! &nbsp; Ongeacht al deze innovaties blijft onze doelstelling steeds het zelfde : U te helpen uw succepercentage te verhogen en uw verkoop te vermenigvuldigen ! U heeft vast reeds begrepen dat met deze nieuwe versie 4.11, Advanced Search &rsquo;nooit eerder zo performant was]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.12.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[249.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/766622-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766622-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Snelle & seriematige bewerking]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/snelle-bewerking/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time! In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category. Look for products that you want to add to this category and add them in one click! You also can control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2889]]></id><name><![CDATA[blockyoutubevideos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Videos - YouTube]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Video's & Muziek]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Breng uw product pagina&#39;s tot leven op uw site en maken ze interactief door het toevoegen van video&#39;s!  De Product Video&rsquo;s - YouTube module is de ideale manier om het succespercentage va]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/video-s-muziek/2889-product-videos-youtube.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2889.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Breng uw product pagina&#39;s tot leven op uw site en maken ze interactief door het toevoegen van video&#39;s!  De Product Video&rsquo;s - YouTube module is de ideale manier om het succespercentage van uw producten te verhogen. Hiermee kunt u eenvoudig en automatisch uw YouTube-video&#39;s importeren en voeg ze in waar u maar wilt op uw productpagina&#39;s.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Video&#39;s zijn een essentieel instrument om uw producten aantrekkelijker te maken en het verbeteren van uw succespercentage. 73% van de consumenten hebben meer kans om een product of dienst te kopen nadat ze een video hebt bekeken.   Deze module is een essentieel instrument voor uw site en uw klanten:Maak uw producten aantrekkelijker door aan uw klanten visuele en relevante aanvullende informatie te verstrekkenVerhoog uw succespercentage en laat retourzendingen verminderen. met 96%. De consument is gemakkelijker te bereiken en neemt sneller een ​​beslissing over een online aankoop als ze kijken naar een video.Verrijk de inhoud van uw site en verbeter uw natuurlijke SEO door het toevoegen van YouTube-video&#39;s op uw product pagina&#39;s.Verbeter de customer engagement en verhogen de gemiddelde winkelwagen grootte op uw site.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.13]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/625269-pprod/product-videos-youtube.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625269-pbig/product-videos-youtube.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanagerforprestashop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Modules]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently!&nbsp;*** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***&nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/modules-prestashop/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently!&nbsp;*** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you.Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!&nbsp;Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management.Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd!&nbsp;Spend an Hour, Save a Day!Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds.For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you.&nbsp;Take Your Online Business to the BankBuy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules.Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[290]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[361.398]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[255.896]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/572842-pprod/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/572842-pbig/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Print Labels Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Voorbereiding & Verzending]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Win kostbare tijd door de uitgifte van uw postetiketten te automatiseren! Bewerk en print uw postetiketten en plak ze direct op de te verzenden bestellingen]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/voorbereiding-verzending/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Win kostbare tijd door de uitgifte van uw postetiketten te automatiseren! Bewerk en print uw postetiketten en plak ze direct op de te verzenden bestellingen. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Win tijd bij de verzending van uw bestellingen.Verlaag het aantal retourzendingen wegens onjuist adres]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595260-pprod/print-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pbig/print-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation...]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[PrestaShop Modules]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/modules-prestashop/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !&nbsp;This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[249.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4731]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestablog]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Professional blog]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Blog, Forum & Nieuws]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best trafic module on prestashop award 2015]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/blog-forum-nieuws/4731-professional-blog.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4731.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best trafic module on prestashop award 2015. The most complete blog published for PrestaShop, Fully compatible with every language and will fit perfectly in your system, whether or not multilingual and/or multishop!&nbsp;Optimized for a better SEO.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get in touch with your customers through a blog has become increasingly common for companies who want to build customer loyalty.No need to install a second cms to get all the features you need, this blog developed by the web agency HDClic is everything you need!&nbsp;Search Engine optimisation (SEO)&nbsp;SEO have been one of the most important part of our developpment of this module,&nbsp;It will be a perfect and infallible tool to increase your visibility on the web.&nbsp;Responsive Design&nbsp;Our webdesign team have developped a template who pefectly integrate in all type of template. Responsive or not.&nbsp;Fast support&nbsp;100% of our customers get an anwser within 1 hour to 12 hours maximum (period days worked) to help you as quickly as possible to implement your project.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/730685-pprod/professional-blog.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/730685-pbig/professional-blog.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/seo-zoekmachineoptimalisatie-vermelding/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO  Internal linking is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a better place on Google.  To optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an internal linking that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.  SEO Internal Linking PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your SEO strategy.  Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!  If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module HTML On Descriptions.  Do we really need internal linking?  Internal linking strategy based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.  Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.  With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.  It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners. SEO Internal Linking is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[189.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sales Reports Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analyses & Statistieken]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/analyses-statistieken/5255-sales-reports-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[*** WINNER OF THE 2015 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  Get perfect visibility on your shop's and products' profitability! The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly,&nbsp;profit and profit margin. Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like "what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?". This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV&nbsp;file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.10.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[189.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/963264-pprod/sales-reports-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963264-pbig/sales-reports-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marktplaats (marketplaces)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/marktplaats/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders. Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le Marché is one of France’s leading marketplaces.  Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success: - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount) - multiple delivery methods, etc.  Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.  1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop module, you no longer need to manage several different back offices. In just a few clicks, connect your PrestaShop site to your Cdiscount store and post your products: - Product descriptions are exported directly to the Cdiscount marketplace, - Prices and inventories are automatically updated, - Your orders will be directly imported and integrated into your PrestaShop store.  Practical and easy configuration! Once you have configured your module, exports are automatic meaning you no longer have any data to handle.  A module developed by an e-merchant for e-merchants! The module’s design is based on the early experience of online retailers. It was created by an e-merchants for the benefit of fellow e-merchants and developed by a team of professional developers, resulting in maximum user friendliness and efficiency.  Free technical support! Your purchase is guaranteed by free technical support provided unconditionally until your products are placed online and your first orders are imported.   *This offer applies for merchants already registered on CleMarché Marketplace and cannot be used in combination with any other ongoing Cdiscount.com offer.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.96]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[159.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[6144]]></id><name><![CDATA[gsnippetsreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Customer Ratings and Reviews Pro + Google Rich Snippets]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful product rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/seo-zoekmachineoptimalisatie-vermelding/6144-customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6144.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful product rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With Google Rich Snippets, benefit from visually enhanced results on Google's search engine results and increase your click rate, numbers visitors and sales ! The full rating and review system will also greatly improve your shop's conversion rate and further increase your sales. If you have already purchased our "Wall Posts" module (sold separately on https://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/4429-wall-posts.html), you can have any rating / review automatically posted on your Facebook page. This module is also fully compatible and integrates with Presta-Module's "Advanced Pack 5" module, available on https://addons.prestashop.com/en/cross-selling-product-bundles/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.4.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[124.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963262-pprod/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963262-pbig/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6291]]></id><name><![CDATA[siretcustomergroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIRET and customer group]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Klantendienst]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/klantendienst/6291-siret-and-customer-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6291.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Finally, you can easily manage your professional customers just by asking their SIRET to transfer them in a client group or there is no tax for example, with prices reduced (e.g. wholesalers)...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/101289-pprod/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/101289-pbig/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6337]]></id><name><![CDATA[codfee]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cash On Delivery With Fee/Surcharge Plus (COD)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Betaling bij Levering]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/betaling-bij-levering/6337-cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6337.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method. More than 5,000 downloads and highly rated!The favourite payment method for your customers!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ESSENTIAL MODULE! This module will increase your sales! You can offset the extra cost of this shipping method by charging a fee to the customer. The cash on delivery payment method allows your customers to pay for the order at the time of receiving their order, they pay on shipment. This payment method is the perfect solution for customers who do not trust other payment methods, such as a card payment or PayPal, and prefer to pay upon receiving their order. With this method, you can offset the additional cost normally associated with "cash on delivery" by charging a fee to customers that choose this payment method. This module allows you to add the "cash on delivery" payment method with the option of applying an extra fee. Compatible with back office orders! Also, you can configure as a pay upon cash on pickup! Customers will benefit from the payment options most used and preferred by them. This module DOES NOT require a monthly fee or any other fee, you buy it once and you use it without any restrictions. Our guarantees ✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote. Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812425-pprod/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812425-pbig/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6344]]></id><name><![CDATA[swissrounded]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Rounded to 5ct for Switzerland]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prijsbeheer]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module enables the management of rounded to 5 cents on your shop. This module is recommended for e-Swiss merchants using PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/prijsbeheer/6344-rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6344.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module enables the management of rounded to 5 cents on your shop. This module is recommended for e-Swiss merchants using PrestaShop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Show prices that are always rounded up to five cents, to avoid confusion when your customers navigate your store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[17.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/882910-pprod/rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/882910-pbig/rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Assign your features as you want]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Zoeken & Filteren]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/zoeken-filteren/6356-multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Add features to your PrestaShop catalog without limits!  With Multiple Features, you can assign as many values as necessary for the same product and the same feature. Remove this PrestaShop limitation and start using your features as you want!  If you also use our layered navigation system Advanced Search 4 (Winner of PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), you can give to your customers a more relevant research in your catalog.  Customer study :  Ocarat.com: "Some jewelry may have a different composition and an alloy of several metals. PrestaShop provides the ability to associate a feature to a product. However, I want to integrate in my shop a gold ring set with diamonds and emeralds. But features tab does not allow me to do so. I can't assign multiple values to a single purpose. So I have to choose between gold, diamonds or emeralds. Multiple Features remove PrestaShop limits and allows you to use features as you want !"]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pprod/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573403-pbig/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6946]]></id><name><![CDATA[invoicepayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[factuur Betaling]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Betaling per Factuur]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[De betaling van de factuur is erg populair in vele landen, hou vooral onder Duitse en Zwitserse klantenMet deze module kunt u de factuur betaalmethode aanbieden aan uw geregistreerde klanten om een ​​]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/betaling-factuur/6946-factuur-betaling.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6946.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[De betaling van de factuur is erg populair in vele landen, hou vooral onder Duitse en Zwitserse klantenMet deze module kunt u de factuur betaalmethode aanbieden aan uw geregistreerde klanten om een ​​veilige shopping ervaring te bieden.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met deze module kunt u een betaling factuur aan uw gebruikers aan te bieden. U kunt bepalen van wat ordersThis betaalmethode is beschikbaar voor uw klanten. Bijvoorbeeld voor uw vaste klanten deze methode shoulderstand beschikbaar zijn vanaf hun 2e orde zijn. U kunt dus bepalen het orderbedrag limiet deze methode beschikbaar is. Verder kunt u de betalingsvoorwaarden te stellen, heeft afhankelijk van de gekozen order status. Nadat de status is veranderd, de betalingstermijn lijkt dan ook in het PDF-factuur. In de configuratie van de module zodat u een textarea voor meer informatie. Bijvoorbeeld, kunt u aangeven waar de klant shoulderstand het geld over te maken. Deze informatie wordt weergegeven in de PDF factuur ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/689390-pprod/factuur-betaling.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689390-pbig/factuur-betaling.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price Increment/Reduction by group, category and more]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Promoties & Geschenken]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With our module you can set the product prices to your customers which do you want to really have]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/promoties-geschenken/7422-price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With our module you can set the product prices to your customers which do you want to really have.&nbsp;Increments, reductions (discounts) and massive fixed price changes with an unlimited conditions and combinations to modify your product prices.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Change the product prices massivelyYou can change the price of the products massively, setting an increment, a discount or a fixed price using these conditions:- Category- Product- Customer group- Customer- Country- Zone- Supplier- Manufacturer- Language- Currency&nbsp;If you choose the percentage type, it can be calculated from Retail or Wholesale price and with or without taxes.To apply the rule, you have this additional controls:&nbsp;- Minimum threshold price- Maximum threshold price- Date From- Date To&nbsp;And also, you can control the final price result setting a minimum and a maximum price with:&nbsp;- Minimum result price- Maximum result price&nbsp;The module adds a priority system in case that two or more rules must be applied to the same product. In this case, you can establish a priority to set the order and if you want to only execute one of this rules (using the option:&quot;Apply only one condition&quot;).&nbsp;&nbsp;Discounts managementTo apply and manage the discounts with our module, you have 3 options:&nbsp;- Show reduction as discount: With this option enabled, the reduction is showed like discount (specific price), then the price of the product will show the old price and the new price with the discount amount/percentage.* Only works if the rule configuration create with our module is a discount.&nbsp;- Skip other discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will not be applied to this product.- Override discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will be applied and the previous discount will be overrided (ommitted but not deleted).This 2 options, are applicable with any of the configurations that you can do with our module.&nbsp;Examples of using the module:- Very useful for the promotions season like Black Friday, Sales, Christmas, Cyber Monday, etc... to change the prices in the products with begin and end date activating and deactivating the offer automatically.- You can set an increment in the catalog products only or a currency (or currencies) to avoid the currency conversion losses.- Set a reduction for a VIP customers group offering them more competitives prices or set an increment to your Resellers group to get more benefits from the products.- Change the prices in a Country or Zone and promote the sales in this geographical area.&nbsp;* The module doesn&#39;t change the original price of the product (you never will lose the original price).&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Attributes filter (combinations)With the new attributes filter you can set the price changes only for an specific product combination.Example: Modify the price only of your product with the L and XL size and not for the prices of the S and M size.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Features filterWith the new features filter you can set the price changes only for products with an specific feature.Example: Modify the price only for the cotton and synthetic products.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Quantity product units filterAdded a new field to set the m&iacute;nimum quantity units of the product that must be in the cart to apply the change in the price.Example: Modify the price of product from 3 units, then, the price of product will be changed automatically only if 3 or more products are added to the cart.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Change the prices within a period (date from and date to)Configure the price changes (increment, discount or fixed price) between 2 dates, or from a date or until a date. It&#39;s an optional field, is not necessary to set a date, if 0 there&#39;s no period limit to apply the rule.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20 until 2016-10-30Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) until 2016-10-30.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Threshold prices to apply the rulesApply the change in your prices only for the product which price is between a threshold.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 10&euro; and less than 30&euro;.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 50&euro;.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is less than 100&euro;.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Minimum and maximum result priceNow, you can set a minimum and a maximum price to get if the result of the increment or discount is below or above this prices.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 200If the result price after the rule application is below 100&euro; (89&euro; for example), the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is above 200&euro; (205&euro; for example) the product price will be 200&euro;.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 0If the result price after the rule application is below 100&euro; (89&euro; for example), the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is 105&euro; the product price will be 105&euro;.Example: Minimum result price = 0 and Maximum result price 100If the result price after the rule application is above 100&euro; (105&euro; for example) the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is 80&euro; the product price will be 80&euro;.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Category tree to select the categoriesNew friendly interface in the Categories selector. Now, the display is in a category tree to select the categories easily.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Friendly multiple selectors interfaceNew friendly multiple selector interface with add and remove buttons and a search box.&nbsp;&nbsp;Geolocation compatibilityFull compatibility with Prestashop Geolocation to change the prices by Zone and Country. If the customer is not logged and the Prestashop Geolocation is enabled, the prices will be shown by the geolocation IP Country of the customer.If logged, the country and the zone calculation is done from the address delivery.&nbsp;&nbsp;Apply a markup or offer a discount in your productsFeel free to play with a markup in the price of your products creating an increment or a reduction configuration by category, by product, by customer group, by customer, by country, by zone, by supplier and by manufacturer.&nbsp;Example: You can create a new category, associate the products to this category and with our module you could set all this category products to 20$ without changing the original product price and without creating complicated discount rules to obtain the desired price.&nbsp;&nbsp;No multistore needed for the same catalog productsThe customers group filter allows to avoid creating a multistore for a B2B and B2C store, sharing the same catalog products but with different prices in each.&nbsp;&nbsp;Our guarantees&nbsp;✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote.&nbsp;Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812413-pprod/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812413-pbig/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7484]]></id><name><![CDATA[newsletterpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Nieuwsbrief & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/nieuwsbrief-sms/7484-newsletter-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7484.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that advertising plays a key role in promoting any business. Using our newsletter will boost your sales faster and easier than any other newsletter module available on the market. This module is an easy and fast way to send customizable newsletters about top selling products or special offers to your clients.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.5.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/724699-pprod/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724699-pbig/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7507]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgsitemaps]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multilingual and Multistore Sitemap Pro – SEO]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Generate sitemaps of all the urls of your store automatically (cron), in all the languages of your store (multilingual), for all your stores (multistore) and including images]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/seo-zoekmachineoptimalisatie-vermelding/7507-multilingual-and-multistore-sitemap-pro-seo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7507.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Generate sitemaps of all the urls of your store automatically (cron), in all the languages of your store (multilingual), for all your stores (multistore) and including images.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve your shop SEO by generating a Sitemaps! Index your shop urls in the search engine (Google, Bing, Ask) quick and easily. With our module, you can automate the generation and configuration of your Sitemaps, so you do not have to worry about.&nbsp;&nbsp;4 types of sitemapsOur module is fully-automatic and allows you to create 4 types of sitemaps:one sitemap that includes all the URLs of your Product pagesone sitemap that includes all the URLs of your Category pagesone sitemap that includes all the URLs of your CMS pagesone sitemap that includes all the URLs of your Manufacturer pages&nbsp;Really easy to configure sitemapsConfigure each type of sitemap separately.Choose the type (product, category, CMS or manufacturer)Choose the store (multistore)Choose the priority of indexation of the urls of the sitemap from 0.1 to 1.0 compared to the urls of your other sitemaps (&quot;priority&quot; tag)Indicate how frequently (daily, weekly, monthly, yearly) the pages contained into the sitemap are supposed to be modified (&quot;changefreq&quot; tag)Choose to include or not the urls of the images into the sitemapChoose to automatically inform or not the search engines Google, Bing and Ask about the sitemap creation (ping request)&nbsp;Really easy to generate the sitemapsClick on the button &quot;Generate&quot; and the sitemaps are generated automatically without overloading the server and without timeout problem. Perfect for large, medium and small catalogues of products.&nbsp;Multistore sitemapsThis module is compatible with PrestaShop monostore and multistore system. It automatically detects all your stores and allows you to easily generate sitemaps for all of them.Please note that the module generate different sitemaps by store, each store has its 4 own sitemaps (Products, Categories, CMS and Manufacturers).&nbsp;Multilingual sitemapsOur module allows you to create sitemaps in all the languages of your store so that you can easily improve the SEO of your store in several languages.For each type of sitemap (products, categories, CMS and manufacturers), the module generates one sitemap that includes the URLS in all languages, as recommended by Google.Our sitemaps are based on Google official guidelines so that you get the best SEO results.&nbsp;Image indexationAnother feature of our module is the possibility to include images into the sitemaps so that Google can index them. It makes your store visible and accessible from Google Image Search, which automatically increases the visibility of your store.&nbsp;Sitemap indexThe module automatically creates a sitemap index to make it easier the management of your sitemaps, as recommended by Google. The index contains all the urls of your sitemaps, you just need to enter the url of the sitemap index into Google Webmaster Tools to submit all your sitemaps at once.&nbsp;Automatic split up of large sitemapsOur module can create sitemaps for all sizes of catalogues. Google only accepts sitemaps that weights up to 10MB or 50,000 urls, this is why our module automatically split up the large sitemaps into several files so that you don&#39;t have any problems in Google.&nbsp;Automatic creation via the CronYou will find inside the module a Cron URL that allows you to generate all your sitemaps automatically and on a regular basis without having to do anything. You just need to copy and paste this url into a Cron module or into your hosting panel to execute these tasks automatically and on a regular basis.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[8066]]></id><name><![CDATA[paybox]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Verifone E-commerce (Paybox) - 1.5, 1.6 & 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Creditcardbetaling of Walletbetaling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Verhoog uw verkoop door&nbsp;veilige pin-/creditcardbetalingen aan te bieden met de module Paybox! &nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/creditcardbetaling-walletbetaling/8066-verifone-e-commerce-paybox-15-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8066.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Verhoog uw verkoop door&nbsp;veilige pin-/creditcardbetalingen aan te bieden met de module Paybox! &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Paybox is bedoeld voor e-commercebedrijven in heel Europa en verwerkt momenteel het betalingsverkeer van ruim 37.000 verkopers en 120 miljoen transactiesper jaar. Met deze betalingsoplossing kunt u dan ook uiteenlopende diensten aanbieden, zoals:betaling in termijnende keuze bieden tussen later, onmiddellijk of bij verzending betalenveiligheid toegespitst op de behoeften van uw webwinkel met selectieve 3D Secure afhankelijk van het winkelmandbedrag van de klanteen oplossing in verschillende talen en voor verschillende valuta om de internationale markt te ontsluitengeavanceerde functionaliteiten van het Flexibele pakket (Paybox System + Direct)een functie voor gedeeltelijke of volledige terugbetaling van een bestelling via de backoffice van PrestaShop]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[184.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611629-pprod/verifone-e-commerce-paybox-15-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611629-pbig/verifone-e-commerce-paybox-15-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8204]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsconnect]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Social Login]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Inloggen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Laat uw klanten via 1 klik eenvoudig registreren en inloggen bij uw winkel via Facebook, Paypal, Amazon, Google of Twitter]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/inloggen/8204-social-login.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8204.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Laat uw klanten via 1 klik eenvoudig registreren en inloggen bij uw winkel via Facebook, Paypal, Amazon, Google of Twitter.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Wist u dat een van de belangrijkste aankoopobstakels op het internet is om verplicht een account aan te moeten maken?&nbsp;Met de module "Social Login" verhoogt u uw conversieratio door uw klanten eenvoudig te laten registreren en in te loggen bij uw winkel via hun favoriete social network: Facebook, Paypal, Amazon, Google of Twitter.  VERMINDER HET AANTAL VERLATEN WINKELWAGENS! Dit is een bekend feit in de wereld van e-commerce, namelijk:&nbsp;hoe minder gedoe tijdens het afrekenen, des te groter de kans dat de klant zijn bestelling afrondt, waardoor het verlaten van de winkelwagen aanzienlijk wordt verminderd. Het gebruik van social networks is aanzienlijk uitgebreid en kent een ongekende groei. Vandaag de dag zijn er&nbsp;meer dan 3 miljard actieve social network-gebruikers wereldwijd.&nbsp;Gebruik deze verbazingwekkende rage in uw voordeel! Dankzij de module "Social Login" kunnen uw klanten zich in&nbsp;slechts één klik&nbsp;registreren en inloggen bij uw winkel. Ze hoeven alleen maar verbinding te maken met hun favoriete social network, zoals Facebook, Paypal, Amazon , Google of Twitter. Dit maakt&nbsp;het bestelproces veel sneller en eenvoudiger.&nbsp;Bovendien is het met PayPal een echte 1-klik registratie omdat PayPal ook automatisch het verzend-/factuuradres van de klant invult in het account van de klant. Maar dat is niet alles! Als u een 1.7 PrestaShop-versie hebt, kunt u zelfs nog verder gaan&nbsp;door deze module te koppelen aan de "One Click Order" -versie van de Presta-module (hier apart verkrijgbaar: https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/bestelproces/29273-one-click-order.html) en aan te bieden aan uw klanten&nbsp;niet alleen&nbsp;om aan te melden met 1 klik maar ook&nbsp;om te bestellen met 1 klik!&nbsp;Een bestelling plaatsen op uw site was nog nooit zo eenvoudig !  [NIEUW] PROFITEER VAN TOTALE VRIJHEID WAT BETREFT HET POSITIONEREN VAN UW CONNECTOREN De module biedt u meerdere mogelijkheden om uw connectoren te positioneren en gaat zelfs zover dat u het precies plaatsen van uw verbindingsknoppen uit handen kunt geven. In feite biedt de module, naast de standaardposities (zie het gedeelte "Functies" van dit productbestand), zoals het gebruikersblok, de inlogpagina of de bestelunnel (voor 1.7 PrestaShop-versies), twee geavanceerde positioneringshulpmiddelen: - HTML-elementen gebruiken:&nbsp;selecteer het HTML-element waarop u de knoppen wilt zien, vul het in in de backoffice en de module zorgt voor alles!- Gebruik voor shortcodes:&nbsp;voor pro, vul uitsluitend een configuratieformulier in en ontvang de shortcode die u rechtstreeks in uw themasjabloon wilt invoegen.  [NIEUW] SNELLE VERBINDINGSBLOKKEN EINDELOOS BEWERKEN Of u nu kiest voor een klassieke of een geavanceerde positie voor uw connectoren, de module biedt u&nbsp;een complete CSS-tool&nbsp;waarmee u het uiterlijk van het verbindingsblok&nbsp;volledig kunt aanpassen. Profiteer van deze geavanceerde functie om uw winkel visueel gezien uniek te maken!  DE SOCIALE INLOGMODULE IS DE MEEST ROBUUSTE EN GRAFISCH ZORGVULDIGE MODULE Deze gloednieuwe "Social Login"-module bevat&nbsp;de nieuwste standaarden&nbsp;van Facebook, PayPal, Amazon, Google en Twitter en verzekert&nbsp;een hoog niveau van kwaliteit en robuustheid. We hebben de interface van de module volledig opnieuw opgebouwd om de configuratie&nbsp;zo aangenaam en intuïtief mogelijk te maken. Ten slotte hebben we ook&nbsp;het ontwerp van de verbindingsknoppen&nbsp;bijgewerkt, zodat u kunt kiezen voor een knoppenstijl die veel moderner is dan voorheen. U hebt de mogelijkheid om uw winkel een moderne stijl te geven. De klassieke knoppenstijl blijft echter beschikbaar.  TREK NIEUWE KLANTEN AAN DOOR ZE KORTING AAN TE BIEDEN IN RUIL VOOR EEN VERBINDING VIA EEN SOCIAL NETWORK Wilt u nieuwe klanten aantrekken? Wat is er beter dan een tegoedbon aan te bieden in ruil voor een snelle verbinding via hun favoriete social network?Ze hoeven geen tijd te verspillen aan het invullen van een registratieformulier, en daarnaast zullen ze&nbsp;profiteren van een voucher.&nbsp;Bestellen wordt enorm vergemakkelijkt! De module geeft u de mogelijkheid deze aanbieding in verschillende posities op uw website&nbsp;te markeren of niet&nbsp;en de toepassingsvoorwaarden&nbsp;rechtstreeks vanuit de backoffice van de module volledig te configureren  Deze module is ontwikkeld door BusinessTech, een gecertificeerde PrestaShop-ontwikkelaar, met meer dan 8 jaar ervaring in het werken met Google en Facebook en 4 keer winnaar van PrestaShop-onderscheidingen. U koopt gegarandeerd een robuuste, betrouwbare en kwalitatieve module. Bovendien beschikken we bij BusinessTech over een snelle en efficiënte technische ondersteuning: wanneer u contact met ons opneemt, spreekt u rechtstreeks met de ontwikkelaars, zodat u zeker weet dat u goed geïnformeerd bent! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963266-pprod/social-login.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/963266-pbig/social-login.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law (Notification Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Juridisch]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/juridisch/8734-eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module fully complies with the European Cookie Law.  Complete compliance with the law  Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information."  Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will.  Main features of the modulesDisplay a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consentDisable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.Fully customize the warning banner (color, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency, buttons...) Getting the user consent   The module includes 2 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled. We recommend you to use this mode, this one allows you to fully comply with the law.Acceptance through the navigation: If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled.Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months)  Customizing the banner content and design  As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store).  The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, color, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background color of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is multilingual and automatically detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language.  Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots crawl you store in order not to affect your SEO.  Disabling the modules that use cookies  This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookies on their computer with their consent.  "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law  To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents.  Multistore mode  The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.5.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pprod/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pbig/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8741]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmulistecommandes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Improved Order List]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Orderbeheer]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/orderbeheer/8741-dmu-improved-order-list.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8741.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The more orders you have to process, the more this module will save you time. As much by the fact that all information is available from the order list and because you will be able to change status in mass with this module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/740079-pprod/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/740079-pbig/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8895]]></id><name><![CDATA[freedeliverymanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Free Delivery Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Verzendkosten]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/verzendkosten/8895-free-delivery-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8895.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction. According to the rules you have chosen, you encourage customers to increase the value of their purchases in order to take advantage of free delivery.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Developing your sales by increasing the value of transactions has never been an easy thing to implement. The &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module is actually the perfect solution for offering your respected customers free shipping through objective rules. It is the promise of a rise in the amount of orders with total control of delivery costs.  The module allows you to calculate in advance, with the help of precise rules, the necessary conditions for unlocking free delivery. The management and monitoring are done according to carriers, delivery area, price, weight, or any other criteria you term as important for your business.  The &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module offers control of delivery costs by releasing delivery available as a function of criteria you have chosen. All the carriers have their own price list. You may, for example, indicate a minimum order amount by carrier In presenting to the customer, in their order summary, the amount remaining before delivery is available, so you definitely encourage them to order more.  Highly detailed statistics visually present two types of reports together. The first one presents the number of orders that have benefited from free delivery, as well as the total and per-order amount that this cost you. You really control the impact of delivery costs. The second report displays the detail of costs caused by free postage and the orders where the rules for free shipping are applied. Thus, the &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module increases the value of transactions as well as the number of orders!  This module has been constantly evolving, many thanks to user feedback. TimActive, in fact, grants great importance to your perception of our solutions and of the improvements that can be added.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/691962-pprod/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/691962-pbig/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8934]]></id><name><![CDATA[migrationpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[MigrationPro: PrestaShop to PrestaShop Migration Tool]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Migratie & Backup]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Upgrade PrestaShop to a latest version or Migrate data between PrestaShops]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/migratie-backup/8934-migrationpro-prestashop-to-prestashop-migration-tool.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8934.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Upgrade PrestaShop to a latest version or Migrate data between PrestaShops. MigrationPro is easy, safe and wicked fast automated module developed for You! You can start migration process in few mins after purchasing. Try the demo now! ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[MigrationPro has been the #1 selling PrestaShop Migrationtool for more than 5 years, making it the most trusted and complete PrestaShop Migration tool on the market. We are dedicated to providing you with the best experience possible. Read below to find out why the sky’s the limit when using MigrationPro. MigrationPro is Automated Shopping Cart Migration Service. Easy, Secure, Fast!CODING KNOWLEDGE not REQUIRED3 minutes setup100% Uptime for source shopThe Most Advanced Options System for MigrationUnlimited usage for one domainUnlimited Entities MigrationPremium Plugins and Features included SAVE $200Keep search rankings & TrafficPreserve Customer's PasswordLower Price - The price is lower than that of our competitorsThe Best Rated Customers Reviews4.5 rating average based on 250+ ratingsDedicated support! Outstanding Support Center. 24hEvery question get an instant answerExtensive DocumentationVideo tutorialsMigrationPro is better! Start update or migrate your PrestaShop NOW! MigrationPro Team & Support Score: Team Expertise: SuperHeroResponse rate: 99.91%Average response time: 2hQuality of Service: 98.97%Total rated: 4.5/5 stars, based 250+ Look at real reviews on the bottom of this page! Please, Don't forget to rate the module after successfully migrating. Customer SuccessScore: Global Customers: 7,500+Satisfied Customers: 98%Stores Migrated: 10,000+Items Migrated 18M+ Join The 7,500+ Satisfied Customers Today How to Successfully Migrate Your Store to PrestaShop? Install the moduleSelect data to migrateStart migration processSuccessfully! Enjoy new PrestaShop GOOD LUCK WITH SALES!  If you are faced with difficulties! We are waiting for you 24h in support!:-)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[migration_tools]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/917724-pprod/migrationpro-prestashop-to-prestashop-migration-tool.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/917724-pbig/migrationpro-prestashop-to-prestashop-migration-tool.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Average Cart Booster (Cross-selling)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Kruisverkoop & Pakketaanbiedingen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Verhoog simpel de gemiddelde waarde van winkelwagens door producten met aanpasbare kortingen in het winkelwagenoverzicht van uw klanten aan te bieden]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/kruisverkoop-pakketaanbiedingen/11345-average-cart-booster-cross-selling.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Verhoog simpel de gemiddelde waarde van winkelwagens door producten met aanpasbare kortingen in het winkelwagenoverzicht van uw klanten aan te bieden.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met behulp van de Push on Cart module:&nbsp;verhoog eenvoudig de gemiddelde winkelwagenwaarde van uw klanten,&nbsp;schoon uw voorraad aan onverkochte producten op,&nbsp;laat klanten nieuwe producten ontdekken en cre&euml;er vraag,vergroot klanttevredenheid en -loyaliteit dankzij aanpasbare kortingen op geselecteerde producten]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.14]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595049-pprod/average-cart-booster-cross-selling.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595049-pbig/average-cart-booster-cross-selling.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13654]]></id><name><![CDATA[hspointofsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[RockPOS - Point-of-sale en omnichannel]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Kassasoftware (POS)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Dankzij RockPOS kunt u nu als webwinkeleigenaar uw producten verkopen in uw fysieke winkels, optentoonstellingen, handelsbeurzen]]></description><author><![CDATA[Hamsa]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/kassasoftware-pos/13654-rockpos-point-of-sale-en-omnichannel.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/13654.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Dankzij RockPOS kunt u nu als webwinkeleigenaar uw producten verkopen in uw fysieke winkels, optentoonstellingen, handelsbeurzen. RockPOS beheert de omnichannel-verkoop op basis van een 2-weg synchronisatie en real-time updates van al uw transacties.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Omnichannel-verkoopRockPOS helpt u bij de koppeling van uw online- en fysieke winkels, en geeft u de mogelijkheid om uw bedrijf via één enkel systeem op verschillende kanalen te beheren. Door het synchroniseren van producten tot bestellingen of klanten, kunt u al uw transacties op alle kanalen tegelijkertijd op een enkele plek bekijken, waardoor u tijd en moeite bespaart, alsmede de klantervaring verbetert. Zo wordt bijvoorbeeld de voorraad in real-time geüpdatet, zodat u kunt zien of er voldoende voorraad is om een volgende bestelling te doen. Verkort het afrekenprocesU wilt natuurlijk niet te veel tijd besteden aan het afronden van een bestelling, maar liever “snel van dienst zijn om meer van dienst te kunnen zijn.” U kunt nu met eeen paar klikken een bestelling afronden, dankzij het duidelijke en gebruiksvriendelijke ontwerp van de RockPOS. Hiernaast kan de RockPOS ook gekoppeld worden aan diverse hardware-apparaten (e.g.: barcode-scanners, kassabonprinters etc.) om transacties snel en soepel te laten verlopen. U heeft nu ook de mogelijkheid om klanten, als ze dat willen, hun artikelen te laten retourneren of om te ruilen. De geretourneerde artikelen worden niet alleen geregistreerd, maar de voorraad wordt ook automatisch bijgewerkt. Bespaart tijd en geldHet opereren van een online- en fysieke winkel kan nu via één systeem, omdat RockPOS gemaakt is als een ingebouwde module voor uw PrestaShop-backoffice. Na de eenmalige aanschaf kunt u het, zonder extra kosten, levenslang gebruiken. Er is geen extra software of speciale training nodig, omdat de RockPOS gemaakt is om een volledig POS te zijn met een duidelijk en simpel ontwerp, zodat iedereen het probleemloos kan gebruiken. U heeft maximaal een half uur nodig om uzelf en uw medewerkers te trainen in het gebruik van de RockPOS, voordat ze zich er vertrouwd genoeg mee voelen om klanten te helpen.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[299.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[379.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[269.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/884358-pprod/rockpos-point-of-sale-en-omnichannel.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/884358-pbig/rockpos-point-of-sale-en-omnichannel.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16535]]></id><name><![CDATA[cartabandonmentpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Abandoned Cart Pro (Herinnering vergeten winkelmand)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Achtergelaten winkelmanden]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Verhoog de conversie met ruim 15% door e-mails voor vergeten winkelmanden te sturen en geef korting om nog meer conversie te bereiken!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/remarketing-achtergelaten-winkelmanden/16535-abandoned-cart-pro-herinnering-vergeten-winkelmand.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Verhoog de conversie met ruim 15% door e-mails voor vergeten winkelmanden te sturen en geef korting om nog meer conversie te bereiken!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatiseer met een paar klikken de verzending van een e-mail ter herinnering aan een vergeten winkelmand.Voeg eenvoudig een korting (of gratis verzending) aan het bericht toe afhankelijk van het winkelmandbedrag om uw conversies te optimaliseren.Maximaliseer de conversie door 1, 2 of 3 herinneringen te versturen wanneer u wilt en in de talen van uw keuze.Profiteer van een intu&iuml;tieve, zeer eenvoudig te configureren tool die volledig aangepast kan worden aan de kleuren van uw webwinkel. Verlies geen twijfelende klanten meer! Maak in een oogwenk automatische e-mails aan ter herinnering aan winkelmanden die niet zijn afgerekend. Opmerkingen: Gepost op 30-08-2014 - ID bestelling:&nbsp;﻿#232568 &quot;de beste module die ik bij prestashop gekocht heb: eenvoudig te installeren en gebruiken, in &eacute;&eacute;n woord geweldig!&quot;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.27]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[134.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[94.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/920927-pprod/abandoned-cart-pro-herinnering-vergeten-winkelmand.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/920927-pbig/abandoned-cart-pro-herinnering-vergeten-winkelmand.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Expert]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Verhoog uw bezoekersverkeer door op de eerste pagina van de resultaten van een zoekmachine te belanden! Deze SEO Expert module vult automatisch beide meta-tags en social media meta tags in om uw webwi]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/seo-zoekmachineoptimalisatie-vermelding/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Verhoog uw bezoekersverkeer door op de eerste pagina van de resultaten van een zoekmachine te belanden! Deze SEO Expert module vult automatisch beide meta-tags en social media meta tags in om uw webwinkel te optimaliseren voor betere zichtbaarheid op zoekmachines en social media platforms.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Maak automatisch meta tags aan en bespaar meer dan 40 uur werk! Met de SEO Expert module:&nbsp; &nbsp;Verschijn op de eerste pagina van zoekresultaten op zoekmachines zoals Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, etc.Vermenigvuldigd uw omzet door toegenomen webverkeer&nbsp;Verbeter de zichtbaarheid in elke taal voor uw winkel&nbsp;Verhoog uw conversies met gekwalificeerde verkeer&nbsp;Maak uw winkel uniek met volledig aangepaste regels voor producten en categorie pagina&#39;s&nbsp;Gebruik Facebook en Twitter om nog meer klanten te werven&nbsp;Optimaliseer uw online winkel voor social media met aangepaste gedeelde titels]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[189.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pprod/seo-expert.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pbig/seo-expert.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17522]]></id><name><![CDATA[lengow]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Lengow]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marktplaats (marketplaces)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Lengow allows you to easily export your product catalogue from your PrestaShop store and sell on Amazon, Cdiscount, Google Shopping, Facebook DPA, Criteo, Ebay, Rakuten, Priceminister&hellip; &nbsp;Ch]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/marktplaats/17522-lengow.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/17522.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Lengow allows you to easily export your product catalogue from your PrestaShop store and sell on Amazon, Cdiscount, Google Shopping, Facebook DPA, Criteo, Ebay, Rakuten, Priceminister&hellip; &nbsp;Choose from our 1,800 available marketing channels!  &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Centralise and manage all of your campaigns for marketplaces, price comparison sites, etc, in the UK and abroad. The simple dashboard allows you to easily manage orders and optimise your performance. Lengow, the European leader in feed management, will be on hand for assistance throughout.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.4.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/598951-pprod/lengow.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/598951-pbig/lengow.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17545]]></id><name><![CDATA[veplatform]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ve | Conversies uit verlaten winkelwagens]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Achtergelaten winkelmanden]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[De enige geautomatiseerde marketingoplossing voor het oplossen van uw verlaat - en conversieproblemen in iedere fase van de customer journey]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/remarketing-achtergelaten-winkelmanden/17545-ve-conversies-uit-verlaten-winkelwagens.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/17545.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[De enige geautomatiseerde marketingoplossing voor het oplossen van uw verlaat - en conversieproblemen in iedere fase van de customer journey. Gebruik Ve vandaag nog met onze gratis 30-dagen trial ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Het Probleem: 98% van uw bezoekers doen de aankoop elders. Daarbovenop is het verlaten van het winkelmandje de rede dat drie van de vier potentiële klanten geen aankoop doet. Ve's oplossing? Verbind met websiteverlatersSpreek verloren klanten aan en haal ze terug naar de siteVerhoog de omzet van de websiteVerbeter de onsite klantervaring Voordelen van Ve: Verander passieve bezoekers in klanten - verbind ze aan uw website als ze deze willen verlaten - verbind ze aan uw website als ze deze willen verlatenSimpel in gebruik - makkelijke setup, onderhoud en transparant geprijsd (afrekenen op prestaties; alleen betalen als de klant converteert)Datagedreven oplossingen - onze inzichten in het klantgedrag helpt ons het juiste bericht op het juiste moment te leverenGecentraliseerde brandmanagement en gepersonaliseerde campagnes - upload uw logo en lettertype voor merkconstitentie en berichtgeving om de campagne te waarborgenGroei met uw bedrijf mee - haal voordeel uit de versterkte en nieuwe features terwijl uw bedrijf groeit Uitgebreide FAQ's - maak gebruik van onze expertise en ervaring]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[17.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/783997-pprod/ve-conversies-uit-verlaten-winkelwagens.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/783997-pbig/ve-conversies-uit-verlaten-winkelwagens.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17711]]></id><name><![CDATA[totswitchattribute]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Enable / Disable a Combination, Import .csv]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Versies & Personalisering van producten ]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to disable a product attribute combinations (without deleting) and activate them whenever you want]]></description><author><![CDATA[202 ecommerce]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/versies-personalisering-van-producten-/17711-enable-disable-a-combination-import-csv.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/17711.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to disable a product attribute combinations (without deleting) and activate them whenever you want. You can update combinations status quickly by importing a list of disabled products via .csv file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA["Enable / Disable a Combination, Import .csv" allows you to disable a combination and then reactivate it when you want without deleting any information.Save time with this module when a product combination is not available or out of stock. Once a declination is temporarily unavailable, most dealers like to hide a combination to avoid frustrating customers. Unfortunately, it is not possible to disable a Prestashop combination (it is necessary to eliminate it). When the combination is available again, you must then recreate it, which is quite time consuming, especially if the above is composed of several attributes, or require a weight or price impact.Our module allows you simply disable combinations (which makes attribute invisible to your customers), and also to enable it at any time and to resume sales !There are two ways to disable/enable product combinations:- manual management,- mass combinations management via .csv import.Enable combinations as quickly as you disabled it: our module allows you to see the summary of disabled combinations and enable them at any time; it is also possible to reactivate combinations directly via product page.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/843379-pprod/enable-disable-a-combination-import-csv.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/843379-pbig/enable-disable-a-combination-import-csv.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18016]]></id><name><![CDATA[supercheckout]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Knowband - One Page Checkout, Social Login & Mailchimp]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Bestelproces]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Mobile responsive One Page Checkout with Facebook/Google+, MAILCHIMP and Ship2Pay feature. It can be used with any theme & any payment method. Compatibility with 30+ Payment & Shipping Methods]]></description><author><![CDATA[Knowband]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/bestelproces/18016-knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18016.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Mobile responsive One Page Checkout with Facebook/Google+, MAILCHIMP and Ship2Pay feature. It can be used with any theme & any payment method. Compatibility with 30+ Payment & Shipping Methods. If it does not work, we fix it for FREE.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Show/Hide any Fields: Decide which fields you want to display on our fast one-page checkout module. This quick checkout module has the functionality to show/hide fields like Company, VAT, Address title etc.&nbsp;Customize buttons: Change our page buttons color to match them with your theme template by using color picker tool of our fast checkout module admin panel. No coding knowledge is required.&nbsp;Mailchimp:&nbsp;Send customer email id directly to Mailchimp either when customer come out from email field or when he place the order after selecting the checkbox for newsletter subscription. If some customer logins via Google or Facebook button, even then his email will be sent to Mailchimp.&nbsp;Change Shipping/Payment method name or image:&nbsp;Our quick checkout module allows admin to change shipping/payment methods name or image easily without any change in the code.&nbsp;Make any field optional: There is an option using which admin can make any field optional or mandatory.&nbsp;Sort address fields: Admin can also manage to sort of all address fields using drag and drop feature. Example: Phone number field can be placed just before First name etc.&nbsp;Drag and Drop: Change position of all blocks using drag and drop features. You can also show payment method first and shipping method below.&nbsp;Ship2pay: Using this feature admin can disable payment methods based on customer shipping method selection.&nbsp;Custom CSS and JS: There is an option in admin panel to add custom CSS and JS. Admin can use this feature to make desired changes without editing core files of one step checkout addon.&nbsp;Custom HTML: This simplified checkout addon also has an option to add multiple custom HTML block at any place. Admin can promote any product, display any promotion OR provide any messages to our customers regarding deal, shipping or payment method information etc.&nbsp;Testing mode: The fast checkout add-on has a testing mode using which admins can test our module on their live site without affecting their ongoing business. If the testing mode is enabled, all customers will go to default checkout of Prestashop and admin can test our module page using a URL which will be shown in our module's admin side.&nbsp;FAQ tab: We understand the value of your time and therefore we have added all basic queries related to our module in our admin panel so that you don't need to contact us for small issues/queries.&nbsp;Custom Fields: System Admin can add any number of custom fields on the checkout page.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/882987-pprod/knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/882987-pbig/knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18656]]></id><name><![CDATA[jmarketplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[JA Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marktplaats opzetten]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/marktplaats-opzetten/18656-ja-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18656.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Best module of Spain in PrestaShop Awards 2015.  This module allows you to integrate several shops in the same economic platform and common retail space. All members can benefit from the sales force other vendors to obtain greater visibility increasing the number of customers and sales.  This integration of sale is currently one of the most effective ways to compete with traditional large surfaces and large ecommerce operators (Amazon, eBay, etc.).  With this module you can join in their market strength of different suppliers to have more visibility and more sales.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[249.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/717058-pprod/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/717058-pbig/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18850]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderedit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Order Edit - Change and Modify existing order]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Orderbeheer]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With this module you can modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/orderbeheer/18850-order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18850.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With this module you can modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Articles information, shipping information, payments and discounts can be modified. Please refer to the screens, the video, the demoshop, or contact us directly in order to get more information on how the module works.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/714564-pprod/order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/714564-pbig/order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18921]]></id><name><![CDATA[mailchimp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Mailchimp Newsletter & Statistics - 1.6 & 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Nieuwsbrief & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Beheer uw nieuwsbrieven heel eenvoudig met Offici&euml;le MailChimp, een module waarmee u uw campagnes vanuit uw PrestaShop Backoffice kunt ontwerpen, versturen en volgen]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/nieuwsbrief-sms/18921-mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18921.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Beheer uw nieuwsbrieven heel eenvoudig met Offici&euml;le MailChimp, een module waarmee u uw campagnes vanuit uw PrestaShop Backoffice kunt ontwerpen, versturen en volgen.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met Offici&euml;le MailChimp:Maakt u geheel aanpasbare nieuwsbrieven van uw webwinkel;Programmeert u uw nieuwsbrieven in &eacute;&eacute;n klik;Bind u uw klanten door uw mailinglijsten via MailChimp te importeren en ze te informeren over aanbiedingen en ander nieuws;Kunt u op elk moment nieuwe klanten aan uw mailinglijsten toevoegen;Kunt u ontvangers segmenteren om campagnes te maken die zo goed mogelijk aansluiten op een bepaalde groep (klanten die op een nieuwsbrief hebben geklikt, enz.);Volgt u uw nieuwsbrieven rustig vanuit uw PrestaShop backoffice dankzij geavanceerde statistieken;Gemak dient de mens: Alle interfaces zijn volledig vertaald!MailChimp telt al meer dan 7 miljoen gebruikers, wacht niet langer! &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[144.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[99.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/645020-pprod/mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/645020-pbig/mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19062]]></id><name><![CDATA[layerslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Creative Slider - Responsive Slideshow]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Gallerijen & Sliders]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Creative Slider is a premium multi-purpose slider to create image galleries, content sliders, and mind-blowing slideshows with must-see effects]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/gallerijen-sliders/19062-creative-slider-responsive-slideshow.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19062.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Creative Slider is a premium multi-purpose slider to create image galleries, content sliders, and mind-blowing slideshows with must-see effects. It uses cutting edge technologies to provide the smoothest experience that’s possible.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Creative Slider comes with more than 200 preset 2D and 3D slide transitions. It has a beautiful and easy-to-use admin interface with supporting modern features like drag 'n’ drop WYSIWYG slider builder, real-time previews, timeline view, Google Fonts and transition builder for custom animations. It’s device friendly by supporting responsive mode, multiple layouts, touch gestures on mobile devices, and uses techniques like lazy load and conditional script loading for optimal performance. You can add any content into sliders, including images, text, custom HTML, YouTube and Vimeo videos or HTML5 self-hosted multimedia contents. It’s also SEO friendly by allowing you to build semantic markup with custom attributes that search engines can index easily. Creative Slider comes with 13 built-in skins, and it hastons of options to entirely customize the appearance and behavior of your sliders at the smallest detail.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.5.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/726345-pprod/creative-slider-responsive-slideshow.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/726345-pbig/creative-slider-responsive-slideshow.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19431]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestanotifypro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pop Promo (Popup)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Dialoogvensters & Pop-ups]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Maak uw aanbiedingen effici&euml;nter!  Met deze pop-in die u binnen een minuut configureert, trekt u onmiddellijk de aandacht van uw bezoekers en maakt u een succes van uw aanbiedingen, sales en flas]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/dialoogvensters-pop-ups/19431-pop-promo-popup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19431.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Maak uw aanbiedingen effici&euml;nter!  Met deze pop-in die u binnen een minuut configureert, trekt u onmiddellijk de aandacht van uw bezoekers en maakt u een succes van uw aanbiedingen, sales en flash sales.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Verhoog uw conversie tijdens aanbiedingen en uw nieuwsbriefaanmeldingen met 20% tot 1000%Zorg ervoor dat niemand uw nieuwe producten mislooptDeze module is in &eacute;&eacute;n minuut te configureren, u kunt dus op elk moment reactief zijn of uw campagnes vooraf programmerenVerklein uw voorraad heel gemakkelijk door middel van speciale aanbiedingen om zo plaats te maken voor nieuwe collecties]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/926172-pprod/pop-promo-popup.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/926172-pbig/pop-promo-popup.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19584]]></id><name><![CDATA[tacartreminder]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Smart Cart Reminder]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Achtergelaten winkelmanden]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/remarketing-achtergelaten-winkelmanden/19584-smart-cart-reminder.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19584.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it. The advanced solution for the abandoned cart reminder is what will fit your reminder emails, your promotions to your customers&#39; cart.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[According to the abandoned cart content, and information about the customers, the Smart Cart Reminder module is the advanced solution that allows you to remind your abandoned carts in an autonomous and focused way.  &laquo;&nbsp;The only module of the cart reminder without subscription offering as many features&nbsp;&raquo; &nbsp;** EMAILS OF REMINDER AND OFFERS ABOUT MARKETING ADAPTED TO EACH CART ** Indeed, the module allows you to create &quot;Reminder rules&quot; according to:Customer information (country, age, gender, group, etc.)Cart contents (amount, products, product categories, stock remaining, etc.)Time of year (Christmas, New Year&rsquo;s, Valentine&rsquo;s Day, Mothers&rsquo; Day, etc.) &laquo;&nbsp;No more untimely and inappropriate promotions which let you feel that you are desperate !&nbsp;&raquo;  With the reminder rules, create easily your own algorithms, for example:  Rule 1&nbsp;: For the cart that exceeds $90, which still contain available items in my stock, the customer is in USA. Then create a discount coupon to obtain the shipping costs for free. Reminder1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Free shipping costs&nbsp;&raquo; email. Reminder2: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only a few days to benefit from the offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 2: For the new customers, create a 5% Off Your Order. Reminder1: 1H after the dropped cart: send the &laquo;To celebrate your arrival 5% Off Your First Order &raquo; email. Reminder2: 24H after Reminder 1: send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only one day left to take advantage of this offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 3: From 15/11/2015 to 25/12/2015(Christmas time), create a coupon to obtain a gift on the order. Reminder 1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Surprise Gift&raquo; email. Reminder 2: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only a few days to benefit from the offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 4: For the cart &gt; &euro;900, the customer is professional Reminder 1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;More information about our catalog dedicated to professional&raquo; email. Reminder 2: Contact the customer by phone  My interest through Smart Cart Reminder module and the reminder rules: &rarr; &nbsp;I increase my sales &rarr; &nbsp;I control the cost of my marketing offers according to the cart &rarr; &nbsp;I approach as close as possible to the desire of my customers &rarr; &nbsp;I gain credibility by creating an intelligent and autonomous system which is no longer seen by my customers as an automatic emails or promotion distributor.  &nbsp;** MANY KINDS OF REMINDER &laquo;&nbsp;STANDARD&raquo; or &laquo;MANUAL&raquo; **&nbsp;Two kinds of reminders to adapt a little more to your reminder process:&laquo;Standard&raquo;: Sending an automatic email with a custom content of the cart to the customer.&laquo;&nbsp;Manual&raquo;: The module notifies you by email to communicate with the customer.You can even set the type of reminder that will suit your cart.  &nbsp;** AN INTERFACE DEDICATED TO &nbsp;&laquo;&nbsp;MANUAL &raquo; REMINDERS (PHONE) **&nbsp;In one page, the module includes all the information of your customers; and includes many features dedicated for your manual reminders.  My interest through&nbsp;my module &laquo;&nbsp;Smart Cart Reminder&nbsp;&raquo; and its page dedicated for manual reminders: &rarr; &nbsp;I don&rsquo;t lose anymore my customers information enabling me converting ( phone number, address, page visited, number of orders placed, current cart &hellip;) &rarr; I win in reactivity through the features present in this unique page: Sending a Pre-formatted email with the link of the complete order, creation of good (s) reduction (s) &rarr; I comment all my telephone conversations  &nbsp;** ADVANCED STATISTICS&nbsp;** &nbsp;The module provides a group of advanced reports easy-to-understand:The evolution of the generated sales according to cart remindersReports about the opened/clicked emailsCart reminder rule conversion reportsReports on employees manually remind customers. This report contains&nbsp;the number of orders made, the number of manual reminder processed for each employee. My interest through statistics is to improve me reminder system: &rarr; &nbsp;I improve my reminder emails to convert the maximum of cart &rarr; &nbsp;I improve my rules to build an autonomous system &rarr; &nbsp;I motivate my employees to increase my sales  &nbsp;** AN INTUITIVE AND EASY MODULE&nbsp;TO TAKE IN CHARGE ** &nbsp;&laquo;&nbsp;A quick start: Coming from a study conducted in the comb to a Committee of a dozen merchants, the module provides a clear and pleasant interface to use. Because we are committed to place the e-trader at the center of the process when we design our modules&raquo;  The module provides a range of features allowing you to act directly on the abandoned cart, you can manually raise without even that the countdown is finished, see explicit details of the choice of a rule for a cart...  My interest through its intuitive and transparent interface &nbsp;&nbsp; I spot in one glance: &rarr; The rules applied on the cart on each abandoned cart &rarr; The time left before the next reminder through the countdown &rarr; The list of reminders applied on the cart &rarr; If the reminder email was been seen and clicked &rarr; If the order was completed &rarr; &nbsp;...  &nbsp;** AN OPERATIONAL MODULE IN SOME CLICKS! ** &nbsp;1 Installation in 1 click and intuitive setting in 2 steps:1. I created my reminder emails, it&rsquo;s easy and fast! Several templates of emails delivered with the module, customize easily and quickly, select an example, edit the colors, edit the text, and here we go! 2- I create my cart reminder rules and I indicate for each rule the reminder emails to send.&nbsp;&nbsp;** A SUPPORT AT YOUR SERVICE&nbsp;**&laquo;Because your time is precious and that we want your full satisfaction!&nbsp;&raquo; &nbsp;You have particular difficulty for the integration, you have some questions. Our team will be glad to support you. We are very sensitive about the responsiveness and the quality of our responses. &nbsp; Source &laquo;&nbsp;addons.prestashop.com&nbsp;&raquo;:&nbsp; From 09/2013 to 08/2015&nbsp; Tickets received: 362 Handled: 362 Our overall service quality: 99.7% ** THEY BOUGHT THE MODULE AND YOU?**  20/08/2015 &laquo;Your module is terrific!!!&nbsp;&raquo;  15/08/2015 - 5/5 &laquo;Great module and great support!&nbsp;&raquo;  28/07/2015 - 5/5 Lots of options to help increase sales. Very friendly and responsive customer service. Highly recommended!  15/07/2015 - 5/5 Very good quality, congratulation.  &laquo;&nbsp;I tried the challenge and I am pleased, congratulations to the developers of this module.&nbsp; I like your system customizing email, this is top!&nbsp;&raquo; Cathy  &laquo;&nbsp;I&#39;m a merchant since 8 years ago, and I gave some ideas. In fact I wanted a new condition to treat new customers differently and according to my stock. A module that I don&rsquo;t leave no more! What flexibility! I paid the purchase in the first week. &raquo;&nbsp;Audrey&laquo;&nbsp;Don&rsquo;t hesitate to share with us your comments!&raquo;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.41]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[189.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pprod/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pbig/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19749]]></id><name><![CDATA[flashsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Premium Flash Sale]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Uitverkoop & Besloten verkoop]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Vergroot de omzet van uw winkel dankzij Flash Sales! De module Flash Sales Premium kan op uw behoeften worden afgestemd en is ideaal om impulsaankopen te genereren]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/uitverkoop-besloten-verkoop/19749-premium-flash-sale.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19749.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Vergroot de omzet van uw winkel dankzij Flash Sales! De module Flash Sales Premium kan op uw behoeften worden afgestemd en is ideaal om impulsaankopen te genereren. U verhoogt uw conversie en komt gemakkelijk van uw voorraad af. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Verhoog uw conversie tot 59% met flash sales!Boost uw verkoop door maximale zichtbaarheid te geven &nbsp;aan uw aanbiedingenMaak uw voorraad snel en effici&euml;nt op om voorraadkosten laag te houdenBreng uw webshop tot leven en zet uw bezoekers aan regelmatig terug te komenZet besluiteloze klanten aan snel een aankoop af te ronden dankzij een beperkte aanbiedingstijd en een countdown-timer&nbsp; Tip:&nbsp; &nbsp;Breng uw klanten op de hoogte van uw flash sales via een newsletter met behulp van de module MailChimp Officiel (56% van de bedrijven zegt een hogere openingsgraad van een newsletter te krijgen tijdens een flash sale-periode) of informeer uw bezoekers zodra ze op uw website komen, met een Pop Promo!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/905699-pprod/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/905699-pbig/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20197]]></id><name><![CDATA[payboxessential]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Verifone E-commerce (Paybox Essential) - 1.5, 1.6 & 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Creditcardbetaling of Walletbetaling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Offer an easy and secure card payment option with our Essentiel&nbsp;Paybox module!  The use of this module requires the subscription of a VAD or VADS contract with your bank]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/creditcardbetaling-walletbetaling/20197-verifone-e-commerce-paybox-essential-15-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20197.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Offer an easy and secure card payment option with our Essentiel&nbsp;Paybox module!  The use of this module requires the subscription of a VAD or VADS contract with your bank.&nbsp;Paybox is compatible with all banks.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This leader card payment solution flows of more than&nbsp;27,000 merchants, and&nbsp;120&nbsp;million transactions&nbsp;each year&nbsp;will allow you to offer a range of services&nbsp;provided in Essentiel&nbsp;PayBox, such as:Payment in multiple stages&nbsp;from the shopping cart amount&nbsp;you configureImmediate or deferred debit Security that is adapted to your store&#39;s needs: 3D Secure system matched to the total order valueA multilingual, multicurrency solution that will help you grow internationally]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[7.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[219.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[144.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/689785-pprod/verifone-e-commerce-paybox-essential-15-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689785-pbig/verifone-e-commerce-paybox-essential-15-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20301]]></id><name><![CDATA[optimalpayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Paysafe / Optimal Payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Creditcardbetaling of Walletbetaling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Paysafe (Former Optimal Payments) makes several million transactions each day]]></description><author><![CDATA[Zedrox]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/creditcardbetaling-walletbetaling/20301-paysafe-optimal-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20301.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Paysafe (Former Optimal Payments) makes several million transactions each day. It supports all major forms of credit card transactions including Visa ®, MasterCard ®, American Express ®, Discover ®, Diners Club ® and JCB ®. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Paysafe (Former Optimal Payments) basic principle is to provide secure payments. As an internationally-oriented Payment Service Provider Paysafe has a lot to offer.Why choose Paysafe Payment gateway:1)Quick and easy to use plugin2)Safe and reliable payment system3)Wide offering of payment options4)Real-time status of payments5)Accept real time payment without leaving your website.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/692431-pprod/paysafe-optimal-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/692431-pbig/paysafe-optimal-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20844]]></id><name><![CDATA[productlabel]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Artikel Labels]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Badges & Logos]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Pas uw site aan en maak uw producten zichtbaarder en aantrekkelijker, door het weergeven van esthetisch aangepaste labelsn op de afbeeldingen voor de items van uw keuze!   De module &ldquo;labels&rdqu]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/badges-logos/20844-artikel-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20844.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Pas uw site aan en maak uw producten zichtbaarder en aantrekkelijker, door het weergeven van esthetisch aangepaste labelsn op de afbeeldingen voor de items van uw keuze!   De module &ldquo;labels&rdquo; van PrestaShop is ideaal voor het aantrekken van de aandacht van uw klanten tijdens de verkoop, en hen te helpen eenvoudig je producten te kopen, nieuwe producten te ontdekken, en de best-sellers uit uw catalogus te herkennen.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Pas uw boodschap en de iconen van uw labels aan om uw verkoop te bevorderen.Vertel uw klanten over speciale functies en kortingen op uw producten. Geef meldingen zoals:&nbsp; &ldquo;nieuwe items&rdquo;, &ldquo;​​1 voor 2&rdquo;, &ldquo;gratis verzending&rdquo;, &ldquo;Aanbod van de maand&rdquo;, &ldquo;de laatsten beschikbaar&rdquo;, etc ...Promoten van uw producten door meer en meer aandacht van uw klanten te trekken met esthetische pictogrammen en labels.Regelmatig vernieuwen van uw site, zonder uw product catalogus te wijzigen.Verbeteren van uw succespercentage met display labels die aankopen te stimuleren.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/715640-pprod/artikel-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/715640-pbig/artikel-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20903]]></id><name><![CDATA[simplesitemap]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sitemap Simple (Multishop, Multilang & Blogs)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sitemap (mult-shop and multi-language), incorporating various blogging modules ! Get rid of an important point by combining SEO and simplicity thanks to this sitemap module ! It’s a plug and play modu]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/seo-zoekmachineoptimalisatie-vermelding/20903-sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20903.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sitemap (mult-shop and multi-language), incorporating various blogging modules ! Get rid of an important point by combining SEO and simplicity thanks to this sitemap module ! It’s a plug and play module ! Compliant with Google standards !  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[  Updated in real time with the latest published pages, fully customizable (you can block specific pages), it will load (for scheduled task) to prevent search engines at desired intervals. This module is multi-language and multishop: All your pages are indexed and listed in the languages ​​defined for each store/.  You can also include images or not, as you can turn off   Sitemap of or remove a link of it. It will also prevent robots (Google among others) the presence of it. It requires no special set-up action and adapts to any environment. Once installed, it's over, it works! No need to think about it! Easily customize the frequency of pages contained in the Sitemap. Automatic priority management is performed, calculated based on website updates.  It's necessary to stabilize a SEO / proper referencing in the ruthless world of the web, it will be an ideal and discreet companion, easy to implement. Simple, effective and very useful, this module is what all modules should do : a good job.  Sitemaps identified all sections of PrestaShop (products, categories, modules, CMS, rewrited URL's and suppliers). Implementation of Blogging modules within separates (for posts and categories) sitemaps too. Optimized SEO / SEO (Google / Bing / Yandex ) to make rapid progress your site to the top. Plug & Play : Once installed, it's ready ! Images included Separate Sitemaps for each shop and each containing selected languages ​​(multi-shop & multi-language) Support 24/7 to your every needs !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/716855-pprod/sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/716855-pbig/sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21273]]></id><name><![CDATA[pqeasypost]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Post Pro (DHL, GLS, DPD, Colissimo, RoyalMail etc)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Voorbereiding & Verzending]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/voorbereiding-verzending/21273-easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21273.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost.com API (Application Programming Interface) into PrestaShop and printing your shipping labels fast and easy. Only 3 cents per label!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that in order to run a successful business you have to optimize it and automatize it as much as possible, this module allows you to do that by increasing the shipping process by 70%.   Think of how long it takes to receive an order from your customers, process the order by adding the products to the package, then connect to your shipping carrier`s software and manually insert the customer information, parcel information and delivery address for the order, for each order at a time. This is very time consuming and it`s very easy to make mistakes because you have a lot of data to process.  With this module all of this is done automatically via the API (Application Programming Interface) that connects the orders section in prestashop with the carrier and instantly sends the information to the carrier, then prints the shipping label which is then slicked to the package. The module supports the most important carriers in the world.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/726515-pprod/easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/726515-pbig/easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21278]]></id><name><![CDATA[popnewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Popup Newsletter]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Dialoogvensters & Pop-ups]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[De meest doeltreffende manier om in contact te blijven met uw klanten! Pop Newsletter maakt een venster aan waarin uw bezoekers worden uitgenodigd om zich in te schrijven op uw nieuwsbrief]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/dialoogvensters-pop-ups/21278-popup-newsletter.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21278.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[De meest doeltreffende manier om in contact te blijven met uw klanten! Pop Newsletter maakt een venster aan waarin uw bezoekers worden uitgenodigd om zich in te schrijven op uw nieuwsbrief. Met deze professionele en volledig aanpasbare pop-in kunt u nieuwe abonnees aantrekken en ze met een korting op hun volgende aankoop ook behouden.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met Pop Newsletter kunt u uw bezoekers een pop-up tonen wanneer ze uw winkel bezoeken. Zet uw bezoekers om in abonnees! &nbsp; Verbeter het abonnementspercentage van uw winkel:  Pop-ups zijn een doeltreffende manier om de aandacht van bezoekers te trekken, want pop-ups ontvangen meer kliks dan schuifknoppen, banners of inschrijvingsvensters onderaan (die hebben namelijk een conversiepercentage van amper 0,05%). De bewezen resultaten van deze tool tonen een stijging tussen 20% en 1.000% van het abonnementspercentage. &nbsp; Zet abonnees om in trouwe klanten: Bied ze een korting voor hun volgende aankoop als dank voor hun inschrijving op uw nieuwsbrief. &nbsp; Zorg voor een naadloze gebruikerservaring: Pop-ins lijken op pop-ups maar bieden een betere gebruikerservaring en passen perfect in de pagina waarin ze verschijnen. Pop Newsletter gebruikt de voor deze reclamemethode aanbevolen beste werkpraktijken:Lichtbox-effectOptie om het modulevenster te sluiten met een klik buiten de pop-in of met een kruisjeskop in de rechterbovenhoek.Optie om te specificeren wanneer de pop-in geactiveerd wordt. Op die manier kan de bezoeker uw site leren kennen voordat hij/zij de pop-in ziet.Nadat de bezoeker de pop-in heeft gesloten, verschijnt de pop-in niet meer.Aanpasbaar aan alle soorten winkels, geen programmerings- of grafische vaardigheden nodig.&nbsp; &nbsp; Verbeter de resultaten van uw nieuwsbrief door uw contactbasis uit te breiden: Dankzij het optionele inschrijvingsformulier voor uw nieuwsbrief kunt u uw abonnees doeltreffender analyseren en classificeren. Met de Pop Newsletter kunt u ook een bevestigingsmail sturen naar het door de abonnee verstrekte e-mailadres om ervoor te zorgen dat de nieuwsbrief niet naar het verkeerde adres wordt gestuurd.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/722395-pprod/popup-newsletter.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/722395-pbig/popup-newsletter.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21318]]></id><name><![CDATA[magicredirect]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Redirections URL (301 / Auto-fixing / Multishop / SEO)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[URL & Omleidingen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Predicts and automatically fix missing pages ! Easily manage all your missing pages and your referrals (404, 301 etc) on your shop (Multi-shop & languages ready)]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/url-omleidingen/21318-redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21318.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Predicts and automatically fix missing pages ! Easily manage all your missing pages and your referrals (404, 301 etc) on your shop (Multi-shop & languages ready). Automaticly redirect disabled and deleted front office pages !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Magic Redirect saves you valuable time by doing for you most actions concerning your redirections (301) and your pages not found (404):Automaticly redirect any disabled/deleted object (products, manufacturers, suppliers, categories, cms pages and categories) to natural parent page.Be warned each new error, but is not intrusive.The module attempts to find internal links that could address these issues. You then have to activate them on the fly.Lead your customers more easily to the right pages.Create rules in the event of major changes on your shop.Lost pages are pre-filled to facilitate your work.Improve your SEO everyday. Google grants a bonus to websites regulating their 404!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/723026-pprod/redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/723026-pbig/redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21510]]></id><name><![CDATA[popexit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pop Exit]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Dialoogvensters & Pop-ups]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Laat een pop-up verschijnen wanneer uw bezoekers op het punt staan om uw website te verlaten om hen aan te moedigen om hun bestelling te voltooien!  Met de module Pop Exit kunt u 25% van de bezoekers ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/dialoogvensters-pop-ups/21510-pop-exit.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21510.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Laat een pop-up verschijnen wanneer uw bezoekers op het punt staan om uw website te verlaten om hen aan te moedigen om hun bestelling te voltooien!  Met de module Pop Exit kunt u 25% van de bezoekers terugwinnen die op het punt staan te vertrekken door hen een tijdelijke (of permanente) korting aan te bieden.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Verminder uw verlaten winkelwagens door uw bezoekers tegen te houden wanneer ze uw website willen verlaten door hen aan te moedigen om hun aankopen te voltooien;&nbsp;Verbeter het conversiepercentage van uw winkel door uw bezoekers een tijdelijke korting aan te bieden, zodat ze worden aangemoedigd om hun aankopen te voltooien;&nbsp;Maak in minder dan 5 minuten een effici&euml;nte en aantrekkelijke on-site retargeting tool  met behulp van de beschikbare professionele designs en de eenvoudig te configureren module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/727469-pprod/pop-exit.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/727469-pbig/pop-exit.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22376]]></id><name><![CDATA[bolplaza]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Bol.com Plaza API connector]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marktplaats (marketplaces)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Gebruik de Bol.com Plaza API direct vanuit Prestashop. Synchroniseert je producten en voorraad naar Bol.com en synchroniseer Bol.com orders naar Prestashop. Volg je eigen proces, en zorg dat Bol]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/marktplaats/22376-bolcom-plaza-api-connector.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22376.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Gebruik de Bol.com Plaza API direct vanuit Prestashop. Synchroniseert je producten en voorraad naar Bol.com en synchroniseer Bol.com orders naar Prestashop. Volg je eigen proces, en zorg dat Bol.com altijd up-to-date is. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Houd je data (product en voorraadinformatie)&nbsp;op Bol.com&nbsp;up-to-date vanuit uw Prestashop omgevingBespaar tijd en kosten door je bestaande proces te gebruiken voor een nieuw kanaalBeheer al je verkoopdata op 1 plekRapporteer automatisch de verzendinformatie naar Bol.comVoorkomt teleurstelling bij klanten wanneer een product uitverkocht is&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[164.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/745548-pprod/bolcom-plaza-api-connector.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/745548-pbig/bolcom-plaza-api-connector.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22553]]></id><name><![CDATA[monkeydata]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[MonkeyData]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analyses & Statistieken]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Gather all your data from sales &amp; marketing channels in one place. Get top-notch online store analytics in the form of clear dashboards]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/analyses-statistieken/22553-monkeydata.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22553.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Gather all your data from sales &amp; marketing channels in one place. Get top-notch online store analytics in the form of clear dashboards.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Top multichannel analytics (data from your online store, marketplaces).Advanced online store analytics - Products, Orders, Customers, Shipping &amp; Payments.FREE mobile app for iOS &amp; Android.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/874833-pprod/monkeydata.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/874833-pbig/monkeydata.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22666]]></id><name><![CDATA[onlinechat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Online Chat]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Ondersteuning & Online chat]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Met de module Online Chat, ontwikkeld door PrestaShop, kunt u in uw webshop eindelijk een online chatmogelijkheid aanbieden om met uw klanten te praten]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/ondersteuning-online-chat/22666-online-chat.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22666.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Met de module Online Chat, ontwikkeld door PrestaShop, kunt u in uw webshop eindelijk een online chatmogelijkheid aanbieden om met uw klanten te praten. Met deze communicatietool, die voor webshops onvermijdelijk is geworden, kunt u een sterkere band met uw klanten opbouwen door ze op het moment zelf te begeleiden en te adviseren bij hun aankopen.   Verbeter de relatie met uw klant dankzij deze module, waarvoor geen abonnement noodzakelijk is, en verhoog uw conversie met 40%! &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Een abonnement is niet nodig, in slechts een paar klikken configureert u uw module en gaat u in gesprek met uw online klanten!&nbsp;U profiteert van een eenvoudige interface die gemakkelijk in het gebruik is en van een vormgeving die perfect is aangepast aan uw site, zowel aan de beheerskant als aan de kant van de winkel zelf.&nbsp;Dankzij uw online gesprekken bouwt u een persoonlijkere en sterkere relatie met uw klanten op en zorgt u ervoor dat uw klanten naar uw merk blijven terugkomen.&nbsp;U vermindert het aantal achtergelaten winkelmandjes, omdat u direct kunt antwoorden op vragen van uw bezoekers.&nbsp;U bent minder tijd kwijt aan het beheer van de aftersales-service, u kunt immers direct aan de slag met problemen en vragen.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/752296-pprod/online-chat.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/752296-pbig/online-chat.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22779]]></id><name><![CDATA[sizeconversion]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Size Guide]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Omvang en eenheden]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Verminder het aantal geretourneede producten en verbeter de klanttevredenheid met de module &nbsp;Size Guide!   Ideaal voor&nbsp;online kleding-, lingerie-, accessoire- en sieradenwinkels, met deze mo]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/omvang-eenheden/22779-size-guide.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22779.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Verminder het aantal geretourneede producten en verbeter de klanttevredenheid met de module &nbsp;Size Guide!   Ideaal voor&nbsp;online kleding-, lingerie-, accessoire- en sieradenwinkels, met deze module kunt u in enkele minuten verschillende maten maken en aanpassen, voor de producten en categorie&euml;n van uw keuze.&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met deze module kunt u maattabellen maken, onmisbare tools om: &nbsp;Aarzelende klanten te helpen om hun aankopen te voltooien&nbsp;door hen de juiste maat te helpen kiezen&nbsp;Het aantal geretourneerde producten en producten die gewisseld moeten worden omdat de maat niet past te verminderen&nbsp;Vermijd ook verlaten winkelwagens en verbeter ook het conversiepercentage van uw winkel]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/755429-pprod/size-guide.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/755429-pbig/size-guide.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23517]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_easyplaces]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Places]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Registratie en Proces van bestellingen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/registratie-proces-van-bestellingen/23517-easy-places.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23517.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature. Help your customers save time and reduce the number of customers who give up whilst creating an account from now on!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our Easy Places module helps you increase your transformation rate by simplifying the order creation process, by providing a feature that automatically enters the account creation or order addresses.  - "OK, but why do I need that ?" - When a new customer wants to place an order on your shop, you have to ask them for their delivery and invoicing address. Your customers find this compulsory and repetitive step annoying and frustrating. Some customers give up and go to another site where they know they have already entered all their information. What is more, shipping errors caused by customers entering their addresses incorrectly are not uncommon, entailing additional transport costs and decreased customer satisfaction owing to the delays caused by their parcels being sent out and returned again.  Easy Places is the ultimate solution for avoiding such problems! It allows you to offer your clients an elegant, high performance technical solution to make your account creation forms more pleasant to fill in.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766068-pprod/easy-places.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/766068-pbig/easy-places.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23617]]></id><name><![CDATA[zendesk]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Official Zendesk]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Klantenservice]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Contextualize your customer interactions by seeing their latest orders when managing tickets inside Zendesk]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/klantenservice/23617-official-zendesk.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23617.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Contextualize your customer interactions by seeing their latest orders when managing tickets inside Zendesk. Order details such as status, total, creation date, and products names and quantities are all visible from within Zendesk.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ This integration will save customer support agents time and contextualize interactions as they no longer need to switch between Prestashop and Zendesk's interfaces to link a ticket to customer orders.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/976308-pprod/official-zendesk.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/976308-pbig/official-zendesk.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23671]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookproductad]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Dynamic Ads]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Achtergelaten winkelmanden]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Take advantage of Facebook&rsquo;s unmatched targeting and ROI with Facebook product ads and remarketing]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/remarketing-achtergelaten-winkelmanden/23671-dynamic-ads.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23671.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Take advantage of Facebook&rsquo;s unmatched targeting and ROI with Facebook product ads and remarketing.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rate and customer repeat purchases on loyalty : Advertise your products on Facebook with Facebook Product Ads by exporting your product catalog to Facebook !&nbsp;&nbsp;*** WINNER OF THE 2017 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***&nbsp;&nbsp;This is essentially the Facebook equivalent of Google Shopping / Merchant Center. But with unprecedented targeting options that Google can only dream of: age, sex, family situation, exact geographical location, interests, groups, pages and products liked, and all the impressive data Facebook has on each and everyone of your customers and prospects. An online marketer&rsquo;s dream come true ! And the cost is also typically lower than Google&rsquo;s, giving you a much better Return On Investment. &nbsp;Just Like Google, Facebook has also implemented a Custom Audiences and Remarketing platform, allowing you to display ads to people who have previously visited your online shop or blog, and segmenting them in any way you see fit. Or you can also acquire new customers that are similar to your existing customers based on the information Facebook has on them and comparing it with information they have on your existing customers. &nbsp;This is all done via the Facebook Pixel code, which also serves to track orders / conversions on your PrestaShop online store. &nbsp;When you mix the Facebook Product Catalog with the Facebook Pixel, you get Dynamic Product Ads: the ability to retarget visitors from your site with the exact products they have viewed or with complementary ones. Dynamic Remarketing is extremely effective and offers a very high conversion rate and ROI.&nbsp;&nbsp;This all-in-one module provides everything you need to get started right now with the world&rsquo;s newest, most advanced and effective online advertising technology on the market. So, get on board TODAY so you don&rsquo;t miss the boat !&nbsp;&nbsp;This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for &quot;Best module&quot;, with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module.&nbsp;Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support&nbsp;: when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[164.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963253-pprod/dynamic-ads.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963253-pbig/dynamic-ads.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23733]]></id><name><![CDATA[beslistcart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Beslist.nl Winkelwagen integratie]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marktplaats (marketplaces)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Publiceer je producten op Beslist.nl en Beslist.be met de Beslist Winkelwagen functionaliteit]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/marktplaats/23733-beslistnl-winkelwagen-integratie.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23733.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Publiceer je producten op Beslist.nl en Beslist.be met de Beslist Winkelwagen functionaliteit. Dit betekent dat jouw klanten de Beslist website niet verlaten, en jij geen trackers hoeft te installeren op je website.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Meer verkopen doordat je meer mensen bereiktGeen noodzaak om de Beslist tracker te implementeren op je websiteGebruik de Beslist Order API (verplicht voor Beslist Winkelwagen)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[189.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/770830-pprod/beslistnl-winkelwagen-integratie.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/770830-pbig/beslistnl-winkelwagen-integratie.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23792]]></id><name><![CDATA[mpeboekhouden]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[e-Boekhouden.nl]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Boekhouding en fakturatie]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[ Gebruik deze module om gemakkelijk je klanten en facturen te exporteren naar e-Boekhouden]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/boekhouding-fakturatie/23792-e-boekhoudennl.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[ Gebruik deze module om gemakkelijk je klanten en facturen te exporteren naar e-Boekhouden.nl]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ Bespaar zeeën van tijd (misschien zelfs een accountant) en gebruik deze module om je te helpen bij het bijhouden van je administratie.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/771895-pprod/e-boekhoudennl.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/771895-pbig/e-boekhoudennl.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23805]]></id><name><![CDATA[dashturnoverbycategory]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Dashboard - Categorieën]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Dashboards]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[U vergroot de prestaties van uw winkel doordat u direct de statistieken van de productcategorie&euml;n van uw catalogus kunt inzien]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/dashboards/23805-dashboard-categorieen.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23805.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[U vergroot de prestaties van uw winkel doordat u direct de statistieken van de productcategorie&euml;n van uw catalogus kunt inzien.&nbsp;U kunt de activiteit van uw e-commercewebsite vanaf het dashboard van uw winkel eenvoudig en direct analyseren, zodat u de verkoop kunt optimaliseren.   Scherp uw aanbiedingen en productbeheer aan,&nbsp;afhankelijk van de resultaten!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[U verhoogt uw conversies&nbsp;doordat u meer grip krijgt op de prestaties van uw winkel.   U bespaart tijd&nbsp;doordat u de belangrijkste statistieken van de categorie&euml;n van uw catalogusproducten tegelijkertijd in &eacute;&eacute;n tabel kunt zien. Eenvoudiger kan niet - en gewoon vanaf het dashboard in uw backoffice!   U bent proactief&nbsp;bij het aanpassen van producten, categorie&euml;n, prijzen en productbeheer en zorgt voor nieuwe reclamecampagnes voor de belangrijkste productcategorie&euml;n.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[19.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[25.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[17.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/772289-pprod/dashboard-categorieen.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/772289-pbig/dashboard-categorieen.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_subscription]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Subscription with automatic recurring payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Abonnementen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A new economic model was created few months ago within the world of e-commerce: subscription-based e-commerce]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/abonnementen/24345-advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A new economic model was created few months ago within the world of e-commerce: subscription-based e-commerce. Known mainly in box form, it is reaching and increasing number of sectors: ready-to-wear clothes, cosmetics, food products...]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Are you ready for subscription-based e-commerce?This is a business model that combines e-commerce and subscription retail. So what is the concept really all about?&nbsp;Subscription-based e-commerce is an excellent way for brands and retailers to begin a process of getting to know their client&egrave;le and establish customer loyalty: the real strength of this economic system is simply its powerful ability to generate customer loyalty!&nbsp;Another advantage is that subscription-based e-commerce enables you to benefit from recurring monthly revenue without having to rely on the acquisition of new customers. What&#39;s more, subscription-based e-commerce encourages consumers to indulge and to re-purchase your products if they are impressed.It stands to reason that there is no-one more loyal than a customer who pays a subscription, but be careful, there are a few down sides to the subscription nowadays: customers are developing an increasing dislike to being tied in. As a result you have to grant him a great deal of freedom; he must be able to cancel his subscription whenever he sees fit!&nbsp;If at the beginning of the month your customer no longer wishes to receive the product or products for which he has subscribed, it should not have to be delivered nor billed for. Nevertheless, the likelihood that the customer will continue to use the service is much more important than is the case with &quot;traditional&quot; e-commerce! It is the assurance of regular monthly turnover, alongside the ability to manage your stock levels.&nbsp;Our Advanced Subscription module for PrestaShop takes into account all of these precepts and saves you the precious time that would be required to implement them manually.&nbsp;The reason that the paid subscription model is developing so quickly within the area of e-commerce is that retail sites appear to find in it an effective solution by which to counteract one of the main issues that chips away at their profitability: delivery fees&nbsp;Amazon Premium, Fnac Express+, Cdiscount &agrave; volont&eacute;... Many e-commerce retailers are now launching their own paid subscription services. In order to grasp the reason behind the phenomenon, one need only remember the fact that delivery fees remain the leading cause of abandoned shopping carts and that, on average, a subscribing customer is twice as lucrative as a non-subscribing customer.&nbsp;A few figures to quantify the impact of delivery on e-business:&nbsp;87% of online shoppers systematically search for a means by which to avoid having to pay shipping fees (searching for a promotional code, addition of a product to the cart...).44% abandon their purchases purely and simply on account of these fees66% switch to a different retail site in search of delivery conditions that are acceptable to them.&nbsp;Converting customers into subscribers enables online retailers to save time and money compared to traditional methods of recovering customers and generating customer loyalty, as it allows you automate part of the customer relationship. This saving can then be allocated to a free delivery service reserved solely for your subscribers, thus eliminating this purchasing deterrent and in turn achieving much greater conversion rates.&nbsp;&nbsp;Objective: to generate long-term customer loyalty&nbsp;In addition to the appeal of novelty, subscription-based e-commerce represents a formidable double-edged sword for brands that are reliant on distribution networks and that are targeting growth. In actual fact, first and foremost the subscription principle allows retailers to generate recurrent turnover and a stable operating account.&nbsp;Thus, while subscription-based e-commerce may have cut its teeth with samples and travel-sized products, various other products now also appear to lend themselves to the model: in ready-to-wear clothing, cosmetics, culture and leisure, but also products intended for regular consumption such as mineral water or hygiene products (baby nappies for instance).&nbsp;&nbsp;Optimization of supply and of your logisticsThe subscription enables you to achieve an improved rate of re-purchase, thus allowing you to purchase from your suppliers more efficiently. In fact, our module will enable you to accurately predict which products will sell, in which quantity and at which frequency.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[499.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[639.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[449.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/783025-pprod/advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/783025-pbig/advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24399]]></id><name><![CDATA[dashbypayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Dashboard - Betaalmethodes]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Dashboards]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[U vergroot de prestaties van uw winkel door te zorgen voor voordelige betaalmethodes die aan de behoeften van uw klanten voldoen!  Geeft een van uw betaalmethodes geen output meer? Het duurt nu geen d]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/dashboards/24399-dashboard-betaalmethodes.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24399.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[U vergroot de prestaties van uw winkel door te zorgen voor voordelige betaalmethodes die aan de behoeften van uw klanten voldoen!  Geeft een van uw betaalmethodes geen output meer? Het duurt nu geen dagen meer voordat u dat in de gaten heeft!&nbsp;  U heeft vanaf uw dashboard direct toegang tot&nbsp;de statistieken van de betaalmethodes van uw winkel.&nbsp;U kunt eenvoudig de prestaties van uw webshop&nbsp;analyseren, uitgesplitst naar de verschillende betaalmethodes die u biedt, zodat u uw verkoop kunt optimaliseren.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[U verhoogt uw conversies&nbsp;doordat u meer grip krijgt op de prestaties van uw betaalmethodes.   U bespaart tijd&nbsp;doordat u de belangrijkste statistieken van uw betaalmethodes tegelijkertijd in &eacute;&eacute;n tabel kunt zien. Eenvoudiger kan niet - en gewoon vanaf het dashboard van uw backoffice!   U bent proactief&nbsp;doordat u de betaalmethodes selecteert die het meest geschikt zijn voor de klanten uit uw doelgroep en brengt deze onder de aandacht op de homepage van uw winkel (dit wekt vertrouwen) en gedurende het aankoopproces.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[19.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[25.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[17.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/784999-pprod/dashboard-betaalmethodes.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/784999-pbig/dashboard-betaalmethodes.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24894]]></id><name><![CDATA[autogoogleplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Address Autocomplete]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Registratie en Proces van bestellingen]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module makes it possible to fill, quickly and without any errors, the address field when yours clients are ordering]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/registratie-proces-van-bestellingen/24894-google-address-autocomplete.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24894.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module makes it possible to fill, quickly and without any errors, the address field when yours clients are ordering. It automatically suggests the right address, and so improve yours customer's browsing comfort. An easy way to save time !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module uses Google Map's API for automatically fill your clients adresses when they register.Increase your turnover, reducing errors and delivery problems.Decrease product returns' number.Improve your user's experience.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Modules Partner Creator"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/798639-pprod/google-address-autocomplete.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/798639-pbig/google-address-autocomplete.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[25758]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoperformance]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Performance (URL Cleaner)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Optimaliseer de SEO van uw winkel in minder dan 5 minuten!  Verwijder gemakkelijk de nummers (id&rsquo;s) in uw URL&rsquo;s en optimaliseer uw pagina&rsquo;s, dit alles terwijl de SEO van uw online wi]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/seo-zoekmachineoptimalisatie-vermelding/25758-seo-performance-url-cleaner.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/25758.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Optimaliseer de SEO van uw winkel in minder dan 5 minuten!  Verwijder gemakkelijk de nummers (id&rsquo;s) in uw URL&rsquo;s en optimaliseer uw pagina&rsquo;s, dit alles terwijl de SEO van uw online winkel wordt verbeterd!  SEO Performance &ndash; URL Cleaner is de enige module die geen overrides gebruikt, wat een verhoogde stabiliteit en compatibiliteit met andere modules garandeert, zonder wijzigingen aan de PrestaShop-kern.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[SEO Performance Module &ndash; URL Cleaner&nbsp;verwijdert automatisch de id&rsquo;s van URL&rsquo;s die PrestaShop standaard maakt op uw product-, categorie- en CMS-pagina&rsquo;s. Het maakt&nbsp;kortere en meer dynamische&nbsp;rechtstreeks omleidingen voor uw nieuwe URL&rsquo;s om de verwijzingen van uw website te optimaliseren.  &bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Verbeter de positie van uw winkel&nbsp;op zoekmachines  Verbeter uw positie op zoekmachines door de URL-schema&rsquo;s van uw product-, categorie- en CMS-pagina&rsquo;s te optimaliseren! &nbsp; &bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bespaar tijd  Met onze module kunt u uw URL&rsquo;s eenvoudig verbeteren. Snelle, intu&iuml;tieve en eenvoudig te gebruiken interface. &nbsp; &bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pas uw URL&rsquo;s veilig aan  Maak gemakkelijk een back-up van uw oude URL&rsquo;s&nbsp;voordat u permanent de URL&rsquo;s van uw winkel aanpast.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/810412-pprod/seo-performance-url-cleaner.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/810412-pbig/seo-performance-url-cleaner.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[25832]]></id><name><![CDATA[lemonway]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Lemon Way for E-commerce ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Creditcardbetaling of Walletbetaling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Cheapest payment solution in Europe. Install in under a minute to start receiving payments immediately. Accept payment by cards from all over the world. Safe and secure. No hidden fees]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/creditcardbetaling-walletbetaling/25832-lemon-way-for-e-commerce.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/25832.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Cheapest payment solution in Europe. Install in under a minute to start receiving payments immediately. Accept payment by cards from all over the world. Safe and secure. No hidden fees.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Secured payments: Secure your payments with 3-D Secureis a payment institution licensed by the Autorité de contrôle prudentiel et de résolution (ACPR) which is attached to the Banque de FranceAnti-fraud systemManage your transactions: One click refund via your back officeYour money is available 24/7Customisable responsive payment pageRate: 1.2% + €0.18 for cards from the European economic area 2.5% + €0.18 for other cardsNo setup fees No management feesNo minimum for transactionsCustomer support:·         Knowledgeable team available to answer your questions quickly]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/812064-pprod/lemon-way-for-e-commerce.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812064-pbig/lemon-way-for-e-commerce.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26203]]></id><name><![CDATA[faviconotification]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Melding tabblad browser (Favicon)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Emails & Notificaties]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Beperk het aantal achtergelaten winkelmandjes in uw webwinkel door een melding toe te voegen aan het tabblad van de browser van uw klanten!   Deze module kan in 30 seconden worden ge&iuml;nstalleerd e]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/emails-notificaties/26203-melding-tabblad-browser-favicon.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26203.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Beperk het aantal achtergelaten winkelmandjes in uw webwinkel door een melding toe te voegen aan het tabblad van de browser van uw klanten!   Deze module kan in 30 seconden worden ge&iuml;nstalleerd en geconfigureerd, en toont het aantal door uw klanten in het winkelmandje gelegde producten. Deze discrete maar effici&euml;nte push herinnert uw gebruikers aan hun winkelmandje en zet hen aan om hun aankopen te be&euml;indigen!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met deze module Melding tabblad browser kunt u: &nbsp;Het aantal achtergelaten winkelmandjes in uw webwinkel beperken door een melding te tonen op het tabblad van hun browser&nbsp;Het conversiepercentage in uw webwinkel moeiteloos verbeteren: u kunt de module met &eacute;&eacute;n klik in uw webwinkel activeren zonder het thema, het design of de navigatie van uw website aan te moeten passen!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/824350-pprod/melding-tabblad-browser-favicon.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/824350-pbig/melding-tabblad-browser-favicon.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26233]]></id><name><![CDATA[user guide prestashop 1.7]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop 1.7 User Guide (English version)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Gebruiksaanwijzing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Meer dan 300 pagina&#39;s en tips in het Engels om u stap voor stap bij te staan! Met de offici&euml;le PrestaShop 1]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/gebruiksaanwijzing/26233-prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26233.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Meer dan 300 pagina&#39;s en tips in het Engels om u stap voor stap bij te staan! Met de offici&euml;le PrestaShop 1.7 Gebruikersgids (Engels) in pdf-formaat leert u hoe u uw webshop gemakkelijk kunt configureren. Maak er gebruik van om uw verkeer, uw verkopen en uw omzet te boosten.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Profiteer volledig van de functionaliteiten die PrestaShop u aanbiedt!Bespaar tijd door uw website op uw duimpje te kennenDeze gebruikersgids leert u alle fijne kneepjes van de functionaliteiten van PrestaShop 1.7. Binnenkort kunt ook u de administratie van uw winkel gemakkelijk beheren via PrestaShop. En weet u hoe u tijd kunt besparen in uw dagelijks beheer, terwijl u uw verkopen omhoog stuwt.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[14.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[16.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[13.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/824674-pprod/prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/824674-pbig/prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26784]]></id><name><![CDATA[todolist]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[To Do List (in your back office)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Dashboards]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Krijg rechtstreeks toegang tot uw taken via het dashboard van uw webwinkel!   Voortaan heeft u nog maar &eacute;&eacute;n softwareprogramma nodig: de module To-dolijst wordt in uw backoffice ge&iuml;n]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/dashboards/26784-to-do-list-in-your-back-office.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26784.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Krijg rechtstreeks toegang tot uw taken via het dashboard van uw webwinkel!   Voortaan heeft u nog maar &eacute;&eacute;n softwareprogramma nodig: de module To-dolijst wordt in uw backoffice ge&iuml;nstalleerd en geeft u de mogelijkheid om taken aan te maken, te bewerken, bovenaan de agenda te zetten en te klasseren om kostbare tijd te besparen!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met de module To-dolijst van PrestaShop kunt u:Alle in uw webwinkel uit te voeren acties via uw dashboard bekijken zonder een beroep te hoeven doen op andere applicatiesTaken bovenaan de agenda zetten in functie van de urgentie van de uit te voeren actiesTijd besparen en uw productiviteit verhogen door de taken te sorteren (lopende bestellingen, aan te vullen voorraden, voor te bereiden aanbiedingen&hellip;)Met &eacute;&eacute;n klik taken aanmakenToegang krijgen tot alle verrichtingen door de voltooide taken in een ander tabblad te bekijkenDe uitvoering van een taak aan een persoon toewijzen die over een werknemersaccount beschikt in de backoffice van uw webwinkel.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/838558-pprod/to-do-list-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/838558-pbig/to-do-list-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26835]]></id><name><![CDATA[buylater]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Wishlist Buy Later (Voor later bewaren)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Verlanglijst & Cadeaubon]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[De toevoeging van &#39;Buy later&#39; (het product registreren voor later) bij het overzicht van uw winkelmand is een belangrijke functie voor grote webwinkels en onmisbaar als u uw verkoop en uw conv]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/verlanglijst-cadeaubon/26835-wishlist-buy-later-voor-later-bewaren.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26835.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[De toevoeging van &#39;Buy later&#39; (het product registreren voor later) bij het overzicht van uw winkelmand is een belangrijke functie voor grote webwinkels en onmisbaar als u uw verkoop en uw conversiepercentage wilt verhogen.  &nbsp; Met &eacute;&eacute;n klik (sneller dan een wensenlijst) zetten uw klanten hun favoriete producten opzij, zodat ze deze bij een volgende bestelling kunnen kopen.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Verbeter de gebruikerservaring, bied bij het overzicht van de producten in het winkelmand een populaire functie aan op de sites van de grootste spelers in e-commerce (Amazon...) ;&nbsp;Verhoog de gemiddelde bestelwaarde van uw klanten: ze waren vergeten dat ze de vorige keer een favoriet opzij hadden gezet, en voegen het product alsnog toe;&nbsp;Verbeter het winkelmand-overzicht, geef uw klanten de mogelijkheid om een lijstje van hun favoriete producten te maken en deze opzij te zetten;&nbsp;Geef uw verkopen een boost, geef uw klanten de mogelijkheid om deze artikelen bij een volgend bezoek weer te bekijken, waarna ze deze heel eenvoudig aan hun winkelmand kunnen toevoegen;&nbsp;Maak van uw klanten trouwe bezoekers door ze de optie te geven om een product dat ze leuk vinden, te bewaren voor hun volgende bestelling;&nbsp;Moedig impulsaankopen aan door een seintje te geven als deze producten in de aanbieding zijn of als ze bijna op zijn]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.7]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/839317-pprod/wishlist-buy-later-voor-later-bewaren.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/839317-pbig/wishlist-buy-later-voor-later-bewaren.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26876]]></id><name><![CDATA[topbanner]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Reclamebanner]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Blokken, Tabbladen & Banners]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Met de module Reclamebanner vergroot u het effect van uw acties en speciale aanbiedingen enorm en genereert u meer verkopen]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/blokken-tabbladen-banners/26876-reclamebanner.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26876.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Met de module Reclamebanner vergroot u het effect van uw acties en speciale aanbiedingen enorm en genereert u meer verkopen. Immers, de in het oog springende reclamebanner met teller moedigt op alle pagina&#39;s op uw site aan tot een aankoop! &nbsp; Communiceer eenvoudig en snel met uw bezoekers tijdens hun hele aankooptraject door de banner, en de tekst erin, te personaliseren.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Breng uw kortingscodes onder de aandacht en zorg zo voor succesvolle reclames, uitverkopen en flitsaanbiedingen.Bijna 60% van de internetters ziet af van de aankoop als ze geen kortingscode zien (onderzoek van Mailorama). Dankzij uw reclamebanner hoeven uw klanten geen enkele aanbieding te missen. Zo wordt hun algemene koopervaring verbeterd. &nbsp;Communiceer eenvoudiger en sneller met uw bezoekers en klantenDe banner is een ideaal communicatiemiddel voor uw gebruikers. U gebruikt hem voor de lancering van een nieuwe collectie, de aankondiging van een speciale aanbieding of bij speciale gelegenheden (Kerst, Black Friday enz.). &nbsp;Geef uw conversies en uw omzet een boostMet de banner die op uw site steeds in beeld is, garandeert u een maximale zichtbaarheid van uw bericht en van de stimulerende elementen (kortingscode, timer). Zo worden uw klanten aangemoedigd hun aankopen te doen voordat de aanbieding afloopt.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/896453-pprod/reclamebanner.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/896453-pbig/reclamebanner.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26877]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoimg]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Images (Alt-tags)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Iets wat vaak vergeten wordt, is de zoekmachineoptimalisatie van de afbeeldingen op productpagina&rsquo;s, wat nochtans een zeer belangrijk element is voor de zichtbaarheid van e-commercewebsites op z]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/seo-zoekmachineoptimalisatie-vermelding/26877-seo-images-alt-tags.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26877.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Iets wat vaak vergeten wordt, is de zoekmachineoptimalisatie van de afbeeldingen op productpagina&rsquo;s, wat nochtans een zeer belangrijk element is voor de zichtbaarheid van e-commercewebsites op zoekmachines.  &nbsp; De module SEO Images (Alt-tags) automatiseer het invullen van ALT-tags van afbeeldingen van uw producten met kwalitatief hoogstaande inhoud en zorgen dus voor een goede positionering van uw websitepagina&rsquo;s.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Bespaar tijd bij zoekmachineoptimalisatie en vergeet nooit meer uw afbeeldingen te optimaliseren door uw ALT-tags automatisch te laten schrijven.  &nbsp; Met de module SEO Images (Alt-tags): &nbsp;Verbeter uw zichtbaarheid op de resultatenpagina&#39;s van zoekmachines&nbsp;Verhoog uw omzet door een betere zichtbaarheid van uw productpagina&rsquo;s&nbsp;Verhoog uw conversiepercentage met gekwalificeerd verkeer&nbsp;Onderscheid u van uw concurrenten met verschillende regels voor de optimalisatie van uw afbeeldingen]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/840258-pprod/seo-images-alt-tags.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/840258-pbig/seo-images-alt-tags.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27274]]></id><name><![CDATA[pscookiebanner]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cookie Banner + CMS]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Juridisch]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The Cookie Policy Banner + CMS developed by PrestaShop helps you meet the EU Cookie law requirements by displaying on your online store a customizable and configurable warning banner in just a few cli]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/juridisch/27274-cookie-banner-cms.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27274.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The Cookie Policy Banner + CMS developed by PrestaShop helps you meet the EU Cookie law requirements by displaying on your online store a customizable and configurable warning banner in just a few clicks. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to be fully in compliance with the European policy of cookies management, informing your customers and prospects of the cookies and other tracers installed on your website&nbsp;It displays a warning banner at the arrival of the visitors on your shop, entirely responsive and customizable, from the formatting of the banner to the displayed text to guarantee a perfect adaptation to your shop.&nbsp;You are accompanied in the creation and redaction of your cookie policy page containing the main information on the use of cookies on your website. A document with useful links is provided to help you write the content of this page.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/873820-pprod/cookie-banner-cms.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/873820-pbig/cookie-banner-cms.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27535]]></id><name><![CDATA[psproductstats]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Geavanceerde productstatistieken (analyses & tips)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Analyses & Statistieken]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[In &eacute;&eacute;n oogopslag heeft u vanuit elke productbeschrijving toegang tot de belangrijkste statistieken en profiteert u van marketingtips en adviezen]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/analyses-statistieken/27535-geavanceerde-productstatistieken-analyses-tips.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[In &eacute;&eacute;n oogopslag heeft u vanuit elke productbeschrijving toegang tot de belangrijkste statistieken en profiteert u van marketingtips en adviezen. Zo verbetert u de prestaties van elk product en geeft u uw verkoop een boost!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Met deze module Statistieken, Producten en Adviezen, ontwikkeld door PrestaShop, vindt u voor elk product, over de gewenste periode: &nbsp; Informatie over de verkoop en de gegenereerde inkomsten van het product:de verkoopcurve;de gegenereerde bruto-omzet;de gegenereerde netto-inkomsten;het profiel van de kopers per:geslacht;leeftijd;land;betalingsvoorkeuren;leveringsvoorkeuren.&nbsp; Vergelijking van de prestaties van dit product met die van andere producten uit dezelfde categorie over de geselecteerde periode, in termen van:Aantal verkochte productenOmzetConversiepercentageAchtergelaten winkelmandenTerugbetalingspercentage]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/880939-pprod/geavanceerde-productstatistieken-analyses-tips.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/880939-pbig/geavanceerde-productstatistieken-analyses-tips.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27562]]></id><name><![CDATA[pshomeslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Homepage-slider]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Gallerijen & Sliders]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Dankzij de module Homepage Slider communiceert u doeltreffend met uw bezoekers door ze een responsieve en full screen slider te tonen op uw homepage! &nbsp; Met deze slider, die u kunt personaliseren ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/gallerijen-sliders/27562-homepage-slider.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27562.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Dankzij de module Homepage Slider communiceert u doeltreffend met uw bezoekers door ze een responsieve en full screen slider te tonen op uw homepage! &nbsp; Met deze slider, die u kunt personaliseren in enkele minuten, moderniseert u uw homepage en trekt u onmiddellijk de aandacht van uw bezoekers zodra ze in uw webshop belanden!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Moderniseer en verrijk uw homepage en houd toch de vormgeving simpel door alle belangrijke inhoud van uw site op een slider te plaatsen in het formaat en de stijl van uw keuze.&nbsp;Zet de informatie van uw keuze in de schijnwerpers en zorg voor een geslaagde communicatiecampagneOf het nu gaat over de lancering van een nieuw product, een aanbieding of de aankondiging van een evenement: met de slider genieten uw berichten van maximale zichtbaarheid op de homepage van uw shop en nodigt u uw bezoekers uit om te blijven snuisteren.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/884765-pprod/homepage-slider.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/884765-pbig/homepage-slider.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[28768]]></id><name><![CDATA[psgiftcards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Premium Cadeaubon 1.6 - 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Verlanglijst & Cadeaubon]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Verdubbel uw klantenbestand en boost uw naamsbekendheid moeiteloos met een cadeaukaart! Bied uw klanten de mogelijkheid het perfecte cadeau te geven dankzij de Gift Card Premium module, ontwikkeld doo]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/verlanglijst-cadeaubon/28768-premium-cadeaubon-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/28768.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Verdubbel uw klantenbestand en boost uw naamsbekendheid moeiteloos met een cadeaukaart! Bied uw klanten de mogelijkheid het perfecte cadeau te geven dankzij de Gift Card Premium module, ontwikkeld door PrestaShop.   Cadeaukaarten zijn praktisch en eenvoudig en het favoriete cadeau van consumenten. De gever slaat nooit de plank mis en de ontvanger kan zelf een keuze maken uit de artikelen in uw winkel!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[E&eacute;n verkoop = 2 klanten! Degene die de cadeaukaart koopt en degene die hem ontvangt. Met deze module kunt u cadeaukaarten aanbieden met een door u gekozen bedrag die uw klanten cadeau kunnen geven aan personen die deze vervolgens in uw winkel besteden. Dit ideale cadeau kan in alle sectoren worden gebruikt (mode, hightech, beauty, sport, reizen, enz.) en valt altijd in de smaak, wat er ook gevierd wordt.  Met Gift Card Premium kunt u:Nieuwe klanten werven tegen lage kosten: ontvangers van cadeaukaarten vormen een markt van vele nieuwe prospects die kunnen worden omgevormd tot trouwe klanten;&nbsp;Uw verkoop verhogen: cadeaukaarten leveren extra omzet op omdat ontvangers vaak meer besteden dan het bedrag op de kaart;&nbsp;Het imago van uw winkel hooghouden: door een win-win situatie te cre&euml;ren met uw gebruikers, verhoogt u de tevredenheid van uw klanten en onderscheidt u zich van uw concurrenten;&nbsp;Besluiteloze klanten over de streep trekken: door een cadeau aan te bieden dat altijd passend is, voldoet u aan de behoeften van zelfs de meest besluiteloze klanten.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/927393-pprod/premium-cadeaubon-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/927393-pbig/premium-cadeaubon-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[28845]]></id><name><![CDATA[totalsavings]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Total Savings (totale besparing)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Promoties & Geschenken]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Verhoog uw verkoop en boost het conversiepercentage van uw winkel door de totale besparing op de aankoop te tonen op het bestellingsoverzicht]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/promoties-geschenken/28845-total-savings-totale-besparing.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/28845.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Verhoog uw verkoop en boost het conversiepercentage van uw winkel door de totale besparing op de aankoop te tonen op het bestellingsoverzicht. &nbsp; Met de Total Savings module kunt u besluiteloze klanten aanzetten tot aankoop en hun gebruikerservaring verbeteren door een gepersonaliseerde banner met het totaal aan kortingen in het winkelmandje te tonen!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Uit onderzoek van de Franse federatie van mailorderbedrijven (Fevad) blijkt dat 15 tot 30% van de achtergelaten winkelmandjes plaats vindt tijdens het bestelproces. Trek uw klanten over de streep door hen de totale besparing te tonen die ze kunnen realiseren dankzij de aanbiedingsartikelen in hun winkelmandje. &nbsp; Zo verhoogt u uw omzet en verbetert u tegelijkertijd de klantervaring dankzij een eenvoudige en transparante prijsaanduiding in hun bestellingsoverzicht.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/935453-pprod/total-savings-totale-besparing.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/935453-pbig/total-savings-totale-besparing.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[29782]]></id><name><![CDATA[pssocialfeed]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[MySocialFeed - Tag uw producten]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Produkten op Facebook & sociale netwerken]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Post de mooiste Instagram-foto&rsquo;s van uw klanten met uw producten in uw winkel!  Maak een hashtag aan voor uw fotogalerij, inspireer uw bezoekers en motiveer de leden van uw community]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/nl/produkten-facebook-sociale-netwerken/29782-mysocialfeed-tag-uw-producten.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-NL&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/29782.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Post de mooiste Instagram-foto&rsquo;s van uw klanten met uw producten in uw winkel!  Maak een hashtag aan voor uw fotogalerij, inspireer uw bezoekers en motiveer de leden van uw community. Als uw bezoekers op de foto&rsquo;s klikken, krijgen ze toegang tot de producten en kunnen ze met een gerust hart aankopen doen. De verkoop in uw webwinkel zal er wel bij varen!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Verhoog uw zichtbaarheid op de sociale netwerken en versterk uw merkimago Uw klanten zijn uw beste ambassadeurs. Betrek hen bij de promotie van uw producten! De bezoekers van uw site zien uw aanwezigheid op sociale netwerken als een vertrouwenwekkend merkteken. Door uw klanten aan te moedigen om uw hashtag aan hun foto&rsquo;s toe te voegen verhoogt u de zichtbaarheid van uw merk op Instagram, vergroot u het aantal abonnees en motiveert u uw community. &nbsp; Vergroot het klantvertrouwen 50% van de internetgebruikers hecht meer belang aan de inhouden die door andere gebruikers worden gepost dan welke via de traditionele communicatiekanalen worden verstuurd (studie van Ipsos en Crowdtap). Met deze module kunt u foto&rsquo;s van uw klanten met uw producten op uw site posten en uw site aldus van betrouwbare kwaliteitsinhouden voorzien. &nbsp; Boost het conversiepercentage van uw winkel Uw klanten kunnen inspiratie opdoen in uw Instagram-album, de foto&rsquo;s van uw producten in hun re&euml;le context bekijken en in &eacute;&eacute;n klik hun beschrijving openen. Ze hoeven zelfs niet meer door uw productcatalogus te bladeren. Het aankoopproces wordt vereenvoudigd wat het conversiepercentage ten goede komt.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.4]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/967721-pprod/mysocialfeed-tag-uw-producten.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/967721-pbig/mysocialfeed-tag-uw-producten.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>